<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon 
	id="skin.metropolis"
	version="3.2.1"
	name="Metropolis"
	provider-name="Amra, Stoli, jingai">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.9.0"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.29"/>
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="6.0.14"/>
		<import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.1.2"/>
		<import addon="script.extendedinfo" version="3.0.1"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.6.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		debugging="false"
		effectslowdown="0.75">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be">A Mix of Retro and Modern. Original Metropolis skin by Amra - continued by Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="da">En blanding af Retro og Moderne.</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Ein Mix aus Retro und Moderne.</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Ένα μείγμα Παλαιού και Νέου. Το αρχικό κέλυφος Metropolis από τον Amra - συντήρηση και εξέλιξη από τον Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="en">A Mix of Retro and Modern.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">A Mix of Retro and Modern.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">A Mix of Retro and Modern.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">A Mix of Retro and Modern.</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Actualización para Eden, una mezcla de Retro y Moderno. Amra, autor original de Metrópolis - continuado por Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Mise à jour pour Eden, un mélange de Rétro et de Moderne. Thème originel de Metropolis par Amra - continué par Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Un mélange de rétro et de moderne</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Unha Mestura do Retro e o Moderno.</summary>
		<summary lang="he">שילוב של רטרו ומודרני.</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Eden-re optimalizálva. A retro és modern stílus ötvözete. Az eredeti Metropolis felszín készítője: Amra -  Stoli folytatja.</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Un Mix di Retrò e Moderno.</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">복고풍과 모던함의 혼합</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">Retro ir modernaus mišinys</summary>
		<summary lang="ms">Campuran Retro dan Modern</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Bijgewerkt voor Eden, een mix van retro en modern. Originele Metropolis skin door Amra - voortgezet door Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="no">En miks av retro og moderne.</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Mieszanka tradycji z nowoczesnością.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Uma Mistura de Retro e Modernidade.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Atualizada para Eden, um Mix de Retro e Modern. Skin Original Metropolis por Amra - continuada por Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Смесь ретро и модерна</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">En blandning av Retro och Modernt.</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">复古与现代的混合体。</summary>
		<description lang="be">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customizable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="da">Metropolis er designet til at vise så mange medier som muligt med læsbar tekst og ikoner. Alt sammen mens skin'et holdes strømlinet og simpelt at bruge for alle familiemedlemmer, med flere temaer og justerbare menuer og visninger. Tak til Hitcher for Alaska Revisited, det er blevet brugt som grundlag for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="de">Metropolis wurde entwickelt, um mit leicht lesbarem Text und Symbolen so viele Medien-Informationen wie möglich darzustellen. Es wird versucht die Anzeige so ausgeglichen und einfach zu halten, um für jedes Familienmitglied mit verschiedenen Themen sowie anpassbaren Menüs und Anzeigen optimal bedienbar zu sein. Dank geht an Hitcher für sein Alaska Revisited, welches als Basis für Metropolis diente.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το Metropolis είναι σχεδιασμένο να εμφανίζει κατά το δυνατόν περισσότερες πληροφορίες πολυμέσων μέσω ευανάγνωστου κειμένου και εικονιδίων. Όλα αυτά ενώ το κέλυφος παραμένει προσιτό και απλό στη χρήση από όλα τα μέλη της οικογένειας, με πολλαπλά θέματα και προσαρμόσιμα μενού και τύπους προβολής. Ευχαριστούμε τον Hitcher για το Alaska Revisited που αποτέλεσε τη βάση για το Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="en">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customizable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customisable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customizable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="es">Metrópolis está diseñada para mostrar en lo posible toda la información multimedia y facilitar la lectura de textos e iconos. Todo ello procurando mantener una piel suave y de fácil uso para todos los miembros de la familia, con múltiples temas, vistas y menús personalizables. Agradecimientos a Hitcher autor de la piel Alaska Revisited, la cual se uso como base para Metrópolis.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Metropolis est conçu pour afficher le plus d'informations multimédia possible avec des icônes et du texte facile à lire. Tout en essayant de conserver douceur et simplicité afin de pouvoir être utilisé par tous les membres de la famille, il intègre de multiples thèmes, des vues et menus personnalisables. Les crédits vont à Hitcher pour Alaska Revisited utilisé comme base pour Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Métropolis est conçu de façon à afficher autant d'information média que possible avec du texte et des icônes faciles à lire, tout en essayant de garder l'habillage aussi fluide et simple à utiliser pour tous les membres de la famille avec plusieurs thèmes et des menus et vues configurables. Crédit à Hitcher pour Alaska Revisité qui fut utilisé comme base pour Métropolis.</description>
		<description lang="hu">A Metropolis arra lett tervezve hogy annyi média infót jelenítsen meg amennyit csak lehet könnyen olvasható szövegekkel és ikonokkal. Mindeközben megpróbálja a felszínt annyira gördülékennyé és egyszerűvé tenni hogy a család minden tagja egyszerűen tudja használni több témával, egyedivé varázsolt menüvel és nézetekkel. Köszönet Hitcher-nek az Alaska Revisited-ért ami a Metropolis alapját adja.</description>
		<description lang="it">Metropolis è stata creata per mostrare quante più informazioni possibili con testi ed icone leggibili. Il tutto cercando di mantenere l'aspetto leggero e semplice da usare per tutti i membri della famiglia, con molti temi, menu personalizzabili e varie visualizzazioni. Un ringraziamento a Hitcher per Alaska Revisited che è stata usata come base per la creazione di Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="ko">Metropolis는 읽기 쉬운 텍스트와 아이콘과 함께 가능한 많은 정보를 표시하도록 디자인 되었습니다. 또한 모든 가족 구성원이 각각의 테마와 사용자 설정 메뉴, 보기를 쉽고 간단하게 사용할 수 있게 유지하고자 노력하고 있습니다. Metropolis의 기초가 된 Alaska Revisited 스킨의 제작자 Hitcher에게 공을 돌립니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt">Metropolis sukurtas taip, kad atvaizduotų kaip galima daugiau media įrašų informacijos su lengvais skaitomu tekstu ir piktogramomis. Visa tai padaryta stengiantis išlaikyti sklandžią teminę išvaizdą, kurią paprasta naudoti visiems šeimos nariams, su keletu temų ir adaptuojamais meniu ir rodiniais. Padėka Hitcher už Alaska Revisited, kuri buvo panaudota kaip pagrindas kuriant Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="ms">Metropolis direka untuk menunjukkan sebanyak mungkin maklumat media dengan cara teks dan ikon. Selain itu cuba kekalkan kelancaran kulit dan keringkasannya untuk diguna dengan pelbagai tema, menu dan paparan yang boleh disuai. Penghargaan buat Hitche atas Alaska Revisited yang mana ia digunakan sebagai dasar Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Metropolis is ontworpen om zoveel media info als mogelijk te tonen met duidelijke tekst en iconen. Alles om de skin zo soepel en makkelijk te gebruiken door alle familieleden met meerdere thema's en aanpasbare menu's en views. Kudo's aan Hitcher voor 'Alaska Revisited', die als basis gebruikt is voor Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="no">Metropolis er utviklet for å vise så mye mediainformasjon som mulig via lettlest tekst og ikoner. Samtidig er tanken å holde temaet polert og enkelt å bruke for alle familiemedlemmer med ulike oppsett og justerbare menyer. Takk til Hitcher over hos Alaska Revisited som er brukt som en base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Metropolis zaprojektowano by pokazywać jak najwięcej informacji o mediach z czytelnymi napisami i ikonami. A wszystko to przy zachowaniu płynności i łatwości użycia przez wszystkich członków rodziny, z wieloma motywami tematycznymi i konfigurowalnymi widokami i menu. Słowa uznania należą się Hitcherowi za skórę Alaska Revisited, która była użyta jako podstawa dla Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="pt">A Metropolis está concebida para exibir tanta info de média quanto possível, com ícones e texto fácil de ler. Ao mesmo tempo, tenta manter um desempenho suave e uma utilização acessível para todos os membros da família, com várias aparências e personalização dos menus e das vistas. O Hitcher merece crédito pela criação de Alaska Revisited, que serviu de base para a Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Metropolis é projetado para exibir o máximo possível de informações da mídia com  textos fáceis de ler e ícones. Tudo ao mesmo tempo tentando manter a pele rápida e simples de usar para todos os membros da família com vários temas e menus customizáveis ​​e modos de visualização. Crédito para Hitcher por Alaska Revisited que foi utilizado como base para Metropolis</description>
		<description lang="ru">Обложка Метрополис запроектирована так, чтобы показывать как можно больше информации о медиа, используя легко читаемые иконки и шрифты. При этом мы стараемся сохранить обложку быстрой и легкой в использовании для всех членов семьи.  Метрополис также предлагает дополнительные темы оформления и настраиваемые меню и режимы просмотра. &#10;Благодарности для Hitcher за его обложку Alaska Revisited, которая была взята за основу Метрополиса. </description>
		<description lang="sv">Metropolis är utformat att visa så mycket mediainfo som möjligt, med text och ikoner som är lätta att läsa. Allt medan skalet är mjukt och enkelt nog att använda för alla familjemedlemmar, med flera teman, anpassningsbara menyer och vyer. Tack till Hitcher för Alaska Revisited som användes som bas för Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="zh">Metropolis旨在展示尽可能多的媒体信息同时尽可能易读的文字和图标。采用多项主题和自定义菜单及视图，同时试图保持皮肤流畅，并且对所有家庭成员都简单易用。感谢Hitcher的Alaska Revisited皮肤，它是Metropolis的基础。</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported (CC BY-NC-SA 3.0) United States License</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=162</forum>
		<website>http://www.floatingpenguins.com</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>http://github.com/jingai/skin.metropolis</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
