<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon 
	id="skin.metropolis"
	version="2.6.3"
	name="Metropolis"
	provider-name="Amra">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.13"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="3.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
		debugging="false"
		effectslowdown="0.75">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be">A Mix of Retro and Modern. Original Metropolis skin by Amra - continued by Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Für Eden angepasst, ein Mix aus Retro und Moderne. Original Metropolis-Skin von Amra - weiterentwickelt von Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Ένα μείγμα Παλαιού και Νέου. Το αρχικό κέλυφος Metropolis από τον Amra - συντήρηση και εξέλιξη από τον Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="en">A Mix of Retro and Modern. Original Metropolis skin by Amra - continued by Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Actualización para Eden, una mezcla de Retro y Moderno. Amra, autor original de Metrópolis - continuado por Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Mise à jour pour Eden, un mélange de Rétro et de Moderne. Thème originel de Metropolis par Amra - continué par Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Eden-re optimalizálva. A retro és modern stílus ötvözete. Az eredeti Metropolis felszín készítője: Amra -  Stoli folytatja.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Bijgewerkt voor Eden, een mix van retro en modern. Originele Metropolis skin door Amra - voortgezet door Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Mieszanka Metro i Modern. Oryginalnie skóra Metropolis stworzona przez Amra - kontynuowana przez Stoli</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Atualizada para Eden, um Mix de Retro e Modern. Skin Original Metropolis por Amra - continuada por Stoli</summary>
		<description lang="be">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customizable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="da">Metropolis er designet til at vise så mange medier som muligt med læsbar tekst og ikoner. Alt sammen mens skin'et holdes strømlinet og simpelt at bruge for alle familiemedlemmer, med flere temaer og justerbare menuer og visninger. Tak til Hitcher for Alaska Revisited, det er blevet brugt som grundlag for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="de">Metropolis wurde entwickelt um so viel wie möglich Medien-Informationen mit leicht lesbarem Text und Symbolen darzustellen. Es wird versucht die Anzeige so ausgeglichen und einfach zu halten um für jedes Familienmitglied mit verschiedene Themen und anpassbare Menüs und Anzeigen optimal bedienbar zu sein. Dank geht an Hitcher für sein Alaska Revisited, welches als Basis für Metropolis diente.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το Metropolis είναι σχεδιασμένο να εμφανίζει κατά το δυνατόν περισσότερες πληροφορίες πολυμέσων μέσω ευανάγνωστου κειμένου και εικονιδίων. Όλα αυτά ενώ το κέλυφος παραμένει προσιτό και απλό στη χρήση από όλα τα μέλη της οικογένειας, με πολλαπλά θέματα και προσαρμόσιμα μενού και τύπους προβολής. Ευχαριστούμε τον Hitcher για το Alaska Revisited που αποτέλεσε τη βάση για το Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="en">Metropolis is designed to show as much media info as possible with easy to read text and icons. All while trying to keep the skin smooth and simple to use for all family members with multiple themes and customizable menus and views. Credit to Hitcher for Alaska Revisited which was used as a base for Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="es">Metrópolis está diseñada para mostrar en lo posible toda la información multimedia y facilitar la lectura de textos e iconos. Todo ello procurando mantener una piel suave y de fácil uso para todos los miembros de la familia, con múltiples temas, vistas y menús personalizables. Agradecimientos a Hitcher autor de la piel Alaska Revisited, la cual se uso como base para Metrópolis.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Metropolis est conçu pour afficher le plus d'informations multimédia possible avec des icônes et du texte facile à lire. Tout en essayant de conserver douceur et simplicité afin de pouvoir être utilisé par tous les membres de la famille. Intègre de multiples thèmes, des vues et menus personnalisables. Les crédits vont à Hitcher pour Alaska Revisited utilisé comme base pour Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Metropolis is ontworpen om zoveel media info als mogelijk te tonen met duidelijke tekst en iconen. Alles om de skin zo soepel en makkelijk te gebruiken door alle familieleden met meerdere thema's en aanpasbare menu's en views. Kudo's aan Hitcher voor 'Alaska Revisited', die als basis gebruikt is voorMetropolis.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Metropolis zaprojektowano by pokazywać jak najwięcej informacji o mediach z czytelnymi napisami i ikonami. A wszystko to przy utrzymaniu skóry płynnej i łatwej do użycia przez wszystkich członków rodziny z wieloma schamatami tematycznymi i konfigurowalnymi widokami i menu. Słowa uznania należą się Hitcher'owi za skórę Alaska Revisited, która była użyta jako baza dla Metropolis.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Metropolis é projetado para mostrar o máximo possível de informações da mídia com  textos fáceis de ler e ícones. Tudo ao mesmo tempo tentando manter a pele rápida e simples de usar para todos os membros da família com vários temas e menus customizáveis ​​e modos de visualização. Crédito para Hitcher por Alaska Revisited que foi utilizado como base para Metropolis</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
