<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
	id="skin.kover"
	version="1.1.0"
	name="KOver"
	provider-name="Jayz2K">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.10.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.6.5" />
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.40"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.30"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1.00" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="16x9" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. A customizable skin. Build your own views and color sets.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. A customizable skin. Build your own views and color sets.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Une skin customisable. Constuisez vos propres vues et palettes de couleurs.</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Pritaikoma pagal poreikius teminė išvaizda. Susikurkite savus rodinius ir spalvų rinkinius.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">KOver [Kodi Overlay]. Uma skin customizável. Construa seus modos de visualização e defina cores.</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">KOver (for KODI Overlay) offers a different approach of KODI skins. Not just purely designed, it also offers to the user the possibility to customize it and make thousands of configurations. KOver embeds two powerful WYSIWYG editors : The Designer and the Color tool. Move, resize, change content and colors ... make it yours !</description>
		<description lang="en_US">KOver (for KODI Overlay) offers a different approach of KODI skins. Not just purely designed, it also offers to the user the possibility to customize it and make thousands of configurations. KOver embeds two powerful WYSIWYG editors : The Designer and the Color tool. Move, resize, change content and colors ... make it yours !</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">KOver (pour KODI Overlay) offre une approche différente des skins KODI. Plus qu'un simple habillage, les utilisateurs peuvent entièrement modifier son apparence et créer des milliers de configurations. KOver intègre deux éditeurs graphiques puissants : Le Designer et l'éditeur de couleurs. Déplacez, redimensionnez, changez les contenus et les couleurs ... faites en votre skin !</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">KOver (KODI Overlay) siūlo kitokį požiūrį į KODI temines išvizdas. Ne tik skaidriai sukurta, bet ir siūlo vartotojui galimybę pritaikyti pagal savo poreikius suteikiant tūkstančius galimų konfigūracijų. KOver turi du galingus WYSIWYG redaktorius: dizainerį ir spalvų įrankį. Perkelkite, pakeiskite dydį, pakeiskite turinį ir spalvas ... susikurkite savo!</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Kover (para KODI Overlay) oferece uma abordagem diferente das demais skins para Kodi. Não apenas puramente projetada, mas também oferece ao usuário a possibilidade de personalizá-lo e fazer milhares de configurações. Kover incorpora dois poderosos editores WYSIWYG: O Designer e a ferramenta Color. Mova, redimensione, altere conteúdos e cores ... Faça você mesmo!</description>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Ползването на мишка и чуствителни на допир монитори не се поддържа</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Mouse and Touch device not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Mouse and Touch device not supported</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Souris et appareils tactiles non pris en charge</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Pelė ir liečiamieji įrenginiai nepalaikomi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Sem suporte a mouse e disposítivos de toque </disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=252</forum>
		<website>https://plus.google.com/communities/101384208271707123426</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/Jayz2K/skin.KOver</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
