<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.apptv" version="1.5.10" name="AppTV" provider-name="Wyrm">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
		<import addon="resource.uisounds.apptv" version="1.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.1.3"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.22"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" effectslowdown="1" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml"/>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de">Ein von Apple TV inspiriertes Skin für Kodi</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Ένα κέλυφος για το Kodi, εμπνευσμένο από το Apple TV</summary>
		<summary lang="en">A AppleTV inspired skin for Kodi</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Un habillage pour Kodi inspiré de l'AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Un habillage pour Kodi inspiré d'AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Un tema para Kodi inspirado no AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="he">מעטפת עבור Kodi בהשראת AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Una skin per Kodi ispirata a AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">애플 TV에 영감을 받은 Kodi용 스킨</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">AppleTV įkvėpta Kodi teminė išvaizda</summary>
		<summary lang="ms">Kulit yang diilham dari AppleTV untuk Kodi</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Een op AppleTV geïnspireerde skin voor Kodi</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Skóra inspirowana interfejsem AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Um tema para o Kodi inspirado na AppleTV</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Uma Skin inspirada na Apple TV</summary>
		<description lang="de">AppTV ist ein vom Apple TV inspiriertes Skin für Kodi. Es bietet eine sehr ressourcensparende, minimalistische Benutzeroberfläche und gleichzeitig Zugang zu den erweiterten Kodi-Funktionen, die nicht in der originalen Apple TV-Oberfläche vorhanden sind.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το AppTV είναι ένα κέλυφος για το Kodi, εμπνευσμένο από το AppleTV. Διαθέτει ένα ιδιαίτερα ελαφρύ, μινιμαλιστικό περιβάλλον εργασίας, ενώ παρέχει πρόσβαση σε ένα πλήθος προχωρημένων λειτουργιών του Kodi που δεν είναι διαθέσιμες στο πρωτότυπο περιβάλλον του AppleTV.</description>
		<description lang="en">AppTV is a AppleTV inspired skin for Kodi. It provides a very light weight minimalist gui while also allowing access to a number of advanced Kodi features not available in the original AppleTV interface.</description>
		<description lang="fr">AppTV est un habillage pour Kodi inspiré de l'AppleTV. Il fournit une interface minimaliste légère tout en permettant l'accès à bon nombre des caractéristiques avancées de Kodi non disponibles dans l'interface AppleTV d'origine.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">AppTV est un habillage pour Kodi inspiré d'AppleTV. Il propose une IUG très légère et minimaliste tout en permettant l'accès à plusieurs fonctions avancées de Kodi qui ne sont pas proposées dans l'interface originale d'AppleTV.</description>
		<description lang="it">AppTV è una skin ispirata a AppleTV per Kodi. Fornisce un'interfaccia molto leggera e minimalistica e permette di accedere ad alcune funzioni avanzate di Kodi non disponibili nell'interfaccia originale di AppleTV.</description>
		<description lang="ko">AppTV는 애플TV에서 영감을 받아 만든 Kodi용 스킨입니다. GUI를 최소화하여 가벼우면서도 애플TV 인터페이스에서는 사용할 수 없는 Kodi의 여러가지 고급 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt">AppTV yra AppleTV įkvėpta teminė išvaizda, skirta Kodi. Ji suteikia labai lengvą, minimalistinę grafinę vartotojo sąsają, tuo pačiu suteikiant galimybę naudoti daugelį pažangių Kdi funkcijų, kurių nėra originalioje AppleTV sąsajoje.</description>
		<description lang="ms">AppTV adalah kulit yang diilham dari AppleTV untuk Kodi. Ia menyediakan gui minimalis yang sangat ringkas juga membolehkan capaian ke beberapa fitur lanjutan Kodi yang tidak tersedia dalam antaramuka AppleTV yang asal.</description>
		<description lang="nl">AppTV is een op AppleTV geïnspireerde skin voor Kodi. het voorziet in een zeer lichtgewichte minimalistische gui terwijl eveneens toegang is tot een aantal geavanceerde Kodi features die niet beschikbaar zijn in de orginele AppleTV interface.</description>
		<description lang="pl">ApplTV jest skórą inspirowaną wyglądem interfejsu AppleTV. Dostarcza wyjątkowo lekki i minimalistyczny interfejs użytkownika umożliwiający dostęp do wielu zaawansowanych funkcji Kodi, niedostępnych w oryginalnym interfejsie AppleTV.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">AppTV é uma skin inspirada na AppleTV para Kodi. Fornece uma GUI bem leve e minimalista  ao mesmo empo que permite acesso a inúmeras funções avançadas do Kodinão disponíveis na interface original da AppleTV.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Poste Funktionswünsche, Fragen und Fehler in [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el">Για βοήθεια, αιτήματα και αναφορές προβλημάτων, μεταβείτε στο [CR]http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Post help and feature/bug requests to [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Postea bugs y preguntas en [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr">Publier les demandes d'aide, de fonction, de bogue sur [CR]http://forum.kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Publier les demandes d'aide, de fonction, de bogue sur [CR]http://forum.kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl">Publica peticións de axuda e características/erros en [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu">Hiba és fejlesztési javaslatot jelezd az alábbi oldalon:[CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it">Chiedi aiuto, richiedi funzioni/segnala bug a [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko">도움 요청, 기능 제안, 버그 보고[CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt">Paprašykite pagalbos ar paskelbkite funkcijos/klaidos užklausą čia: [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms">Poskan bantuan dan permintaan fitur/pepijat ke [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl">Stuur help en functie/fout vragen naar [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl">Prośby o pomoc, zgłoszenia błędów oraz prośby o nowej funkcje zamieść na forum[CR]http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Postar pedidos de ajuda/funcionalidades e bugs em  [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv">Posta hjälp-/funktionsförfrågningar samt buggrapporter till&#10;[CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh">请在论坛发布求助及功能需求/报告错误 [CR]http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.Kodi.org/forumdisplay.php?fid=76</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/wyrm65/skin.apptv</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot003.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot004.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot005.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot006.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot007.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot008.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot009.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot010.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>1.5.10[CR]  - Major work on navigation thruout the skin.[CR]  - Changes to how Classical music is shown thruout the skin.[CR]  - Major expansion of focused items indicators thruout the skin.[CR]</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
