<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.rapier"
  version="4.2.0"
  name="Rapier"
  provider-name="Scarfa">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.watchlist" version="0.1.8"/>
    <import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="1.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension 
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt" 
    effectslowdown="0.75"
    debugging="false"/>
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Rapier skin by Scarfa.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Rapier autorstwa Scarfa.</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Rapier από τον Scarfa.</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Rapier 스킨 제작: Scarfa.</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Rapier skin por Scarfa.</summary>
    <description lang="en">The goal is to provide a simple to use but clean and elegant interface that focuses on efficiency when browsing your media. Important considerations are put on usability, performance, and providing the user with flexibility when it comes to customization. Rapier tries to support all the latest features XBMC has to offer as long as it fits in with the skin's design goals.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Celem jest dostarczenie prostego w użyciu, a jednocześnie przejrzystego i eleganckiego interfejsu, wydajnego podczas przeglądania mediów. Szczególny nacisk położono na użyteczność, wydajność oraz zapewnienie użytkownikowi elastyczności w jej konfiguracji. Rapier stara się obsługiwać wszystkie najnowsze funkcje, jakie XBMC ma do zaoferowania, tak długo, jak pasują one do celów projektowych skóry.</description>
    <description lang="el">Στόχος είναι η παροχή ενός απλού στη χρήση, καθαρού και κομψού περιβάλλοντος που εστιάζει στην απόδοση κατά την περιήγηση των πολυμέσων σας. Έχει δοθεί έμφαση στην χρηστικότητα, στην απόδοση, και στην παροχή στο χρήστη ευέλικτων δυνατοτήτων προσαρμογής. Το Rapier προσπαθεί να υποστηρίξει όλες τις τελευταίες δυνατότητες που προσφέρει το XBMC, αρκεί να ταιριάζουν με τους στόχους του σχεδιασμού του.</description>
    <description lang="ko">효율적으로 미디어를 탐색할 수 있으면서도 멋있고 우아한 인터페이스를 제공려는 것이 스킨의 목적입니다. 사용성, 성능과 사용자화의 유연성을 고려하여 제작되었습니다. Rapier는 스킨의 디자인 목적에 부합하는 XBMC의 모든 최신 기능을 지원하려 합니다.</description>
    <description lang="es">El objetivo es ofrecer una interfaz sencilla, limpia y elegante que se centra en la eficacia cuando se navega por los medios. Un gran esfuerzo se ha puesto en la sencillez, el rendimiento y ofrecer al usuario la flexibilidad en cuanto a personalización. Rapier trata de apoyar todas las últimas caracteristicas disponibles de XBMC, siempre y cuando se ajuste al diseño de la piel.</description>
    <disclaimer></disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
