<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.rapier" version="11.2.60" name="Rapier" provider-name="Scarfa, Gade">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.9"/>
	<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="6.0.10"/>
	<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.1.3"/>
	<import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.22"/>
	<import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.2"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" effectslowdown="0.75" debugging="false">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Rapier от Scarfa и Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Grafický vzhled vytvořili Scarfa a Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Rapier skin af Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Rapier-Skin von Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Rapier από τον Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Rapier skin by Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Rapier skin by Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Rapier skin by Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Rapier skin by Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Rapier skin por Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Rapier-ulkoasu. Tekijöinä Scarfa ja Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Rapier par Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Habillage Rapier par Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Tema Rapier por Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">המעטפת Rapier של Scarfa ו־Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Rapier felszín Scarfa-tól és Gade-től</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Rapier skinn eftir Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Skin Rapier di Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Rapier 스킨 제작: Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Rapier teminė išvaizda, sukurta Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Rapier oleh Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Rapier skin av Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Rapier skin door Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Rapier autorstwa Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Rapier skin  por Scarfa,Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Tema Rapier por Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Costumul Rapier de Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Rapier vzhľad od Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">Rapier skin โดย Scarfa, Gade.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Scarfa、Gade 设计的 Rapier 皮肤。</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">由Scarfa, Gade所開發的Rapier佈景主題</summary>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Обликът е създаден с цел да предостави лесен, изчистен и елегантен интерфейс, фокусиран върху ефикасност при преглеждане на мултимедийното съдържание. Предвидени са множество опции за персонализиране. Стреми се към поддържане на всички функции на Kodi, стига те да не се разминават с целта на облика.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Målet er at levere en grænseflade, der er simpel at anvende, ren, elegant og fokuserer på effektivitet, når du browser dine medier. Vigtige overvejelser er gjort i forbindelse med brugervenlighed, ydelse og levering af fleksibilitet for brugeren, når det kommer til tilpasning. Rapier forsøger at understøtte alle de nyeste funktioner, Kodi har at tilbyde, så længe det stemmer overens med skin'ets design-mål.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Ziel war es, ein einfaches zu benutzendes aber klares und Elegantes Interface zu erschaffen, das sich auf Effizienz beim durchsuchen deiner Medien konzentriert. Besonderes Augenmerk wurde auf Benutzerfreundlichkeit, Performance und dem Benutzer eine möglichst hohe Flexibilität bei der Anpassbarkeit zu bieten gelegt. Rapier versucht die neuesten Funktionen von Kodi zu unterstützen solange es mit diesen Zielen zu vereinbaren ist.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Στόχος είναι η παροχή ενός απλού στη χρήση, καθαρού και κομψού περιβάλλοντος που εστιάζει στην απόδοση κατά την περιήγηση των πολυμέσων σας. Έχει δοθεί έμφαση στην χρηστικότητα, στην απόδοση, και στην παροχή στο χρήστη ευέλικτων δυνατοτήτων προσαρμογής. Το Rapier προσπαθεί να υποστηρίξει όλες τις τελευταίες δυνατότητες που προσφέρει το Kodi, αρκεί να ταιριάζουν με τους στόχους του σχεδιασμού του.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">The goal is to provide a simple to use but clean and elegant interface that focuses on efficiency when browsing your media. Important considerations are put on usability, performance, and providing the user with flexibility when it comes to customization. Rapier tries to support all the latest features Kodi has to offer as long as it fits in with the skin's design goals.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">The goal is to provide a simple to use but clean and elegant interface that focuses on efficiency when browsing your media. Important considerations are put on usability, performance, and providing the user with flexibility when it comes to customisation. Rapier tries to support all the latest features Kodi has to offer as long as it fits in with the skin's design goals.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">The goal is to provide a simple to use but clean and elegant interface that focuses on efficiency when browsing your media. Important considerations are put on usability, performance, and providing the user with flexibility when it comes to customization. Rapier tries to support all the latest features Kodi has to offer as long as it fits in with the skin's design goals.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">El objetivo es ofrecer una interfaz sencilla, limpia y elegante que se centre en la eficacia cuando se navega por el contenido. Se ha puesto un gran esfuerzo en la sencillez, en el rendimiento y en ofrecer al usuario la flexibilidad en cuanto a personalización. Rapier trata de soportar todas las últimas caracteristicas disponibles de Kodi, siempre y cuando se ajuste al diseño del skin.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tavoitteena on tarjota helppokäyttöinen ja siisti käyttöliittymä, joka keskittyy tehokkaaseen median selaamiseen. Erityistä huolta on nähty käytettävyyden, suorituskyvyn ja muokattavuuden varmistamiseksi. Rapier pyrkii tukemaan kaikkia Kodin viimeisimpiä ominaisuuksia kunhan ne sopivat ulkoasun tyyliin.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Le but est de fournir une interface facile à utiliser mais propre et élégante, se concentrant sur l’efficacité lorsque vous parcourez votre contenu multimédia. Les considérations importantes sont la convivialité, la performance et de fournir à l’utilisateur une souplesse de personnalisation. Rapier essaie de prendre en charge toutes les dernières fonctions offertes par Kodi tant quelles s’ajustent aux buts conceptuels de l’habillage.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">L'objectif est de proposer une interface simple mais aussi propre et élégante mettant l'accent sur l'efficacité pour parcourir vos médias. Les priorités sont l'ergonomie, la performance, et offrir la plus grande flexibilité à l'utilisateur à l'heure de la personnalisation. Rapier tente de prendre en charge les toutes dernières fonctionnalités de Kodi tant que ces dernières correspondent aux objectifs de l'habillage.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A cél egy könnyen kezelhető, tiszta és elegáns felület ami a médiaböngészés hatékonyságára fókuszál. Fontos szempont a használhatóság, teljesítmény és a rugalmas testreszabhatóság. A felszín fejlesztési céljainak figyelembevételével a Rapier törekszik a Kodi legújabb funkcióinak támogatására.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">L'obiettivo è quello di fornire un'interfaccia semplice da usare, pulita ed elegante, focalizzata sulla navigazione efficiente dei propri media. Sono tenute in particulare considerazione usabilità, performance e la giusta flessibilità nella personalizzazione. Rapier cerca di supportare tutte le caratteristiche offerte da Kodi, fintanto che si integrano con gli obiettivi di design della skin.</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">효율적으로 미디어를 탐색할 수 있으면서도 멋있고 우아한 인터페이스를 제공하는 것이 스킨의 목적입니다. 사용성, 성능, 사용자 설정의 유연성을 고려하여 제작되었습니다. Rapier는 스킨의 디자인 목적에 부합하는 Kodi의 모든 최신 기능을 지원하려 합니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Tikslas yra pateikti paprastą naudoti, tačiau neperkrautą ir elegantišką sąsają, kuri pagrindinį dėmesį skiria efektyvumui naršant media įrašus. Daug dėmesio skirta patogumui ir našumui, tuo pačiu suteikiant vartotojui lankstumą, pritaikant teminę išvaizdą pagal savo poreikius. Rapier stengiasi palaikyti visas naujausias Kodi funkcijas, jei tik jos atitinka teminės išvaizdos dizaino tikslus.</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Matlamat adalah untuk pengggunaan mudah serta antaramuka yang kemas dan elegan yang berfokuskan pada kecekapan melayari media anda. Pertimbangan utama adalah kebolehgunaan, prestasi, dan menyediakan fleksibiliti bila membuat penyuaian. Rapier cuba menyokong semua fitur terkini Kodi sediakan dengan syarat ia menepati matlamat rekabentuk kulit.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Het doel is om te voorzien in een simpel te gebruiken maar schone elegante interface dat zich focust op efficiëntie wanneer je door je media zoek. belangrijke afwegingen zijn gezet op gebruikersgemak, prestaties, en voorzien de gebruiker met flexibiliteit wanneer het komt bij aanpasbaarheid. Rapier probeert de laatste functies die Kodi heeft te ondersteunen. zolang het past in de skin's ontwerpdoelen.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Celem jest dostarczenie prostego w użyciu, a jednocześnie przejrzystego i eleganckiego interfejsu, skupionego na efektywności przeglądania mediów. Szczególny nacisk położono na użyteczność, wydajność oraz zapewnienie użytkownikowi elastyczności w jej konfiguracji. Rapier stara się obsługiwać wszystkie najnowsze funkcje jakie Kodi ma do zaoferowania, tak długo, jak pasują one do celów projektowych skóry.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O objetivo é proporcionar algo simples de usar, mas também uma interface limpa e elegante  que se concentra na eficiência ao navegar em sua mídia. Considerações importantes são colocados em usabilidade, desempenho e proporcionando ao usuário a flexibilidade quando se trata de personalização. Rapier tenta apoiar todas as últimas características que Kodi tem a oferecer, desde que ele se encaixa com os objetivos do design da skin.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Cieľom je poskytnúť používateľsky jednoduché, ale aj čisté a elegantné rozhranie, ktoré sa zameriava na efektivitu pri prehliadaní vašich médií. Hlavný ohľad sa kladie na použiteľnosť, výkonnosť a poskytnutie používateľovi flexibilitu, pokiaľ ide o prispôsobenie. Rapier sa pokúša podporiť všetky najnovšie funkcie, ktoré Kodi ponúka, pokiaľ vyhovuje dizajnovým cieľom vzhľadu.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">สกินนี้มาพร้อมกับแนวคิดที่ต้องการให้ผู้ใช้สามารถใช้งานง่ายอีกทั้งดูดีและสะอาดตาโดยมุ่งเน้นที่ให้เลือกดูมีเดียต่างๆได้อย่างมีประสิทธิภาพ โดยจุดสำคัญที่โฟกัสคือสามารถใช้งานได้ครบถ้วนหลากหลาย, สมรรถนะการทำงานที่รวดเร็วและให้ความยืดหยุ่นเมื่อต้องมีความการกำหนดค่าด้วยตนเอง อีกทั้ง Rapier จะพยายามให้การสนับสนุนทุกๆ Feature ใหม่ที่ Kodi มีให้ให้สามารถใช้งานได้ตราบเท่าที่มันยังคงไม่ขัดต่อแนวคิดของสกินนี้</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">我们的目标是提供一个简洁易用，注重媒体浏览效率的界面。重点关注可用性、性能和提供用户定制的灵活性。Rapier 力求支持所有符合此皮肤设计目标的 Kodi 最新特性。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">以提供易用且清晰優雅的介面為宗旨，致力於讓使用者能夠更有效率的瀏覽媒體檔案。考量重點在於可用性、效能及高度客製化可能性。只要符合本佈景主題的設計宗旨，我們將力求支援最新版Kodi提供的所有功能。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=120</forum>
    <website>https://kodi.wiki/view/Add-on:Rapier</website>
    <source>https://github.com/gade01/Rapier</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
	  <banner>resources/banner.jpg</banner>
      <clearlogo>resources/clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-10.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <news>[B]11.2.60[/B][CR]- Fix buttons for randomizing playlist content[CR][I]For a full list of changes visit https://raw.githubusercontent.com/gade01/Rapier/Leia/changelog.txt[/I]</news>
  </extension>
</addon>
