<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.mediastream_redux"
  version="2.0.0"
  name="MediaStream Redux"
  provider-name="Jezz_X (graphics by team razorfish)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="1.0">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Jezz_X's redesign of the original "MediaStream" skin</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">MediaStream Redux, o reinventar do tema 'MediaStream' por Jezz_X</summary>
    <description>   MediaStream Redux is a complete remake from the ground up of Team Razorfish's MediaStream skin and only uses the original skins graphics (also its home window layout and some of its views) and is for 16x9 only no 4x3 support like the original.[CR]   I made this skin because coming from the Project Mayhem skins I loved the original Mediastream skin looks but found it very hard to navigate my way around in the original (old habits die hard). So this skin Navigates more like the PM skins (Menu is on the left hand side)[CR]  All credit to Team Razorfish for the original concept and graphics used in this version</description>
    <description lang="pt">   O tema MediaStream Redux é um completo reinventar do tema 'MediaStream', desenvolvido originalmente pela equipa Razorfish. Apenas usa alguns gráficos e organização de vistas do tema original, exclusivamente para ecrãs 16x9.[CR]   Desenvolvi este tema após o términos dos temas 'Project Mayhem'. Adorava o tema 'Mediastream' original mas achava muito difícil navegar nos menus (velhos hábitos fazem o monge). Assim, ao navegar, este tema comporta-se como os temas 'Project Mayhem' (Menus à esquerda).[CR]  Todos os créditos vão para a equipa 'Razorfish' pelo conceito original e gráficos usados nesta versão.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
