<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<strings>
	<!-- Name Of Skin -->
	<string id="31000">Revolve</string>

	<!-- Home Menu Text -->
	<string id="31001">Live TV</string>
	<string id="31003">TV Shows</string>
	<string id="31004">Books</string>
	
	<string id="31020">Play your</string>
	<string id="31021">Watch</string>
	<string id="31022">Predict the</string>
	<string id="31023">Manage your</string>
	<string id="31024">Do a skin</string>
	<string id="31025">Leave through the</string>
	<string id="31026">Enjoy your</string>
	<string id="31027">Read your</string>
	<string id="31028">Change your</string>
	<string id="31029">Wait until the</string>

	<string id="31080">Settings Menu</string>
	<string id="31081">Exit Menu</string>
    
	<!-- Other Menu / Control Options -->
	<string id="31100">Run</string>
	<string id="31101">PVR</string>
	<string id="31102">New</string>
	<string id="31103">Memory Used</string>
	<string id="31104">Clear playlist</string>
	<string id="31105">Order:</string>
	<string id="31106">Navigation options</string>
	<string id="31107">Playlist/Library options</string>
	<string id="31108">Slideshow options</string>
	<string id="31109">Settings options</string>
	<string id="31120">Home Menu Items</string>
	<string id="31121">Options in Home Menu:</string>
	<string id="31122">Background Visuals</string>
	<string id="31123">Background music visualisation</string>
	<string id="31124">Background video playback</string>
	<string id="31125">Default Add-ons</string>
	<string id="31126">Default lyrics script</string>
	<string id="31128">Faded background images</string>
	<string id="31129">Faded music visualisation</string>
    <string id="31130">Faded video playback</string>
    <string id="31131">Background images and pictures</string>
	<string id="31132">Miscellaneous Settings</string>
	<string id="31133">Debug Settings</string>
	<string id="31134">Show debug grid</string>
	<string id="31135">Show debug information</string>
	<string id="31136">Edit custom option</string>
	<string id="31137">Show Side Menu when it is not focused</string>
	<string id="31138">Show 'No information available' messages</string>
	<string id="31139">Settings level:</string>
	<string id="31140">Custom Option</string>
	<string id="31141">Reset all skin settings to default</string>
	<string id="31142">Edit action</string>
	<string id="31143">Show scrollbar in views when it is not focused</string>
	<string id="31144">Show media flag icons</string>
	<string id="31145">Show artwork thumbnail when playing media</string>
	<string id="31146">Skin Information</string>
	<string id="31147">Changelog</string>
	<string id="31148">Credits</string>
	<string id="31149">Show the Revolve Title Screen on startup</string>
	<string id="31150">Show descriptions in Landscape view</string>
	<string id="31151">Show back button</string>
	<string id="31152">Group items in the Side Menu</string>
	<string id="31153">Location:</string>
    <string id="31154">Show background behind overlays</string>
	<string id="31155">Show names in Thumbnails and Panels views</string>
	<string id="31156">Show help in settings windows</string>
    
    <string id="31160">Enable the Music Videos option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if your library contains at least one music video.</string>
    <string id="31161">Enable the display of images, both Revolve artwork and fanart, in the background.</string>
    <string id="31162">Enable the fading of the images that are shown in the background. Faded background images improve the readability of the information on screen.</string>
    <string id="31163">Enable music visualisation in the background. If music visualisation is disabled, Revolve will display background images (if those are enabled).</string>
    <string id="31164">Enable the fading of music visualisation in the background. Faded music visualisation improves the readability of the information on screen.</string>
    <string id="31165">Enable video playback in the background. If video playback is disabled, Revolve will display background images (if those are enabled).</string>
    <string id="31166">Enable the fading of video playback in the background. Faded video playback improves the readability of the information on screen. Full screen video playback is not affected by this setting.</string>
    <string id="31167">Edit this pre-defined option. You can set the action that is executed when this option is chosen in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31168">Enable this custom option in the Home Menu. You should provide a name and an action to make this custom option do something useful.</string>
    <string id="31169">Edit this custom option. You can set the name and subtitle of the option, and you can enter the action that is executed when this option is chosen in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31170">Enable the Books option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31171">Enable the Games option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31172">Enable the Favourites option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31173">Enable the Videos option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31174">Enable the Movies option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if your library contains at least one movie.</string>
    <string id="31175">Enable the TV Shows option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if your library contains at least one tv show.</string>
    <string id="31176">Enable the Music option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31177">Enable the Pictures option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31178">Enable the Programs option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31179">Enable the Weather option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31180">Enable the File Manager option in the Home Menu.</string>
    <string id="31181">Enable the Add-ons option in the Home Menu. You can always manage your add-ons through the Add-ons option in the Settings menu.</string>
    <string id="31182">Enable the Settings option in the Home Menu. You should realize that it is hard to change these settings without this option!</string>
    <string id="31183">Enable the Exit option in the Home Menu. You might need this option to exit Kodi.</string>
    <string id="31184">Do not completely hide the side menu when it is not focused. An invisible side menu gives Revolve a cleaner look, but there is no longer a visual clue that suggests the presence of a side menu.</string>
    <string id="31185">Enable the Live TV option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if the Personal Video Recorder (PVR) features are enabled. You can enable these PVR features in the Live TV settings.</string>
    <string id="31186">Show the 'No information available' messages if there is no information available.</string>
    <string id="31187">Enable the (Play) Disc option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if there is a disc in the drive of your Kodi device.</string>
    <string id="31188">Do not completely hide the scrollbar in the views when it is not focused. An invisible scrollbar gives Revolve a cleaner look, but there is no longer a visual clue that suggests the presence of the scrollbar.</string>
    <string id="31189">Enable the Albums option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if your library contains some music.</string>
    <string id="31190">Set the add-on that can provide lyrics for your music.</string>
    <string id="31191">Show the artwork for the currently playing media in the lower right corner of the screen in most Kodi windows. Hiding this artwork gives Revolve a cleaner but slightly boring look.</string>
    <string id="31192">Enable an on-screen grid that you can use to place and align elements of this skin.</string>
    <string id="31193">Enable on-screen debug information that shows the currently active window and dialogs.</string>
    <string id="31194">Show the media icons that give detailed information about resolution, video codec, audio codec, aspect ratio, etc. in most views. Showing these icons gives you more information about the highlighted media, but hiding these icons gives Revolve a cleaner look.</string>
    <string id="31195">Reset all Revolve specific skin settings to the default values. This will delete all skin specific settings, including your custom Home Menu options!</string>
    <string id="31196">Reload the current skin. This option is useful if you change the skin files while Kodi is running.</string>
	<string id="31197">Circle Items</string>
	<string id="31198">Movie Source</string>
	<string id="31199">Episode Source</string>
	<string id="31200">Album Source</string>
	<string id="31201">Set the source of the movie information that is displayed inside the circle of the Home Menu. Some sources require an add-on; these sources are unavailable when this add-on is not installed. The movie information is accessible from the 'Movies' option in the Home Menu (press left when 'Movies' is selected). If you select 'Nothing', the movie information will be unavailable.</string>
	<string id="31202">Set the source of the episode information that is displayed inside the circle of the Home Menu. Some sources require an add-on; these sources are unavailable when this add-on is not installed. The episode information is accessible from the 'TV Shows' option in the Home Menu (press left when 'TV Shows' is selected). If you select 'Nothing', the episode information will be unavailable.</string>
	<string id="31203">Set the source of the music album information that is displayed inside the circle of the Home Menu. Some sources require an add-on; these sources are unavailable when this add-on is not installed. The album information is accessible from the 'Albums' option in the Home Menu (press left when 'Albums' is selected). If you select 'Nothing', the album information will be unavailable.</string>
	<string id="31204">Always open in root folder</string>
	<string id="31205">Make this Home Menu option always open in the root folder. Some Home Menu options remember the last opened library or folder. These options reopen the view in this library or folder, and not in the root folder. You can bypass this behaviour with this setting. Activating this setting will always open the library in the root folder.</string>
	<string id="31206">Show or hide the Revolve title screen on start-up.</string>
	<string id="31207">Choose the busy animation for the progress bars.</string>
	<string id="31208">Select a busy animation:</string>
	<string id="31209">Show the description of the currently selected item (like movies or albums) in the Landscape views. Showing the description gives you more information about the selected item, but hiding the description shows more fanart in the background.</string>
    <string id="31210">Enable the TV option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if the Personal Video Recorder (PVR) features are enabled. You can enable these PVR features in the Live TV settings.</string>
    <string id="31211">Enable the Radio option in the Home Menu. This option will only be visible in the Home Menu if the Personal Video Recorder (PVR) features are enabled. You can enable these PVR features in the Live TV settings.</string>
    <string id="31212">Enable on-screen debug information that shows the borders of the hidden lists in some views.</string>
    <string id="31213">Enable a back button (in some views) to improve mouse navigation in Revolve. With this back button you can close the active view and return to a previous window.</string>
    <string id="31214">Group the items in the Side Menu in logical units with a small header.</string>
    <string id="31215">Draw a single color background behind the overlay information to increase the readability of the currently playing media.</string>
    <string id="31216">Show the names of the unfocused thumbnails in the Thumbnails and Panels views. This gives the Thumbnails and Panels views a more cluttered look, but it is easier to navigate these views.</string>
	<string id="31217">Background animation level:</string>
	<string id="31218">Select an animation level for animations in the background. These (useless) animations can be visible in the background of some views, around messages and in dialog windows.</string>
	<string id="31219">Show or hide the help text in all the Settings windows.</string>
	<string id="31220">Choose shape of icons in Thumbnails view:</string>
	<string id="31221">This category contains the settings for how the backgrounds are handled.</string>
	<string id="31222">This category contains the settings for how the options in the Home Menu are displayed. This includes turning options on or off, customizing pre-defined options, and adding new custom options.</string>
	<string id="31223">This category contains the settings for how the circle menu inside the Home Menu is displayed. This includes the sources that populate these circle menus.</string>

	<string id="31227">This category contains the settings for the default addons that Revolve uses.</string>
	<string id="31228">This category contains miscellaneous settings that are used in Revolve. Several visual aspects of the Revolve skin can be configured here.</string>
	<string id="31229">This category contains the debug settings for Revolve.</string>
	<string id="31230">This category contains information about Revolve, including access to the changelog and the credits.</string>
	<string id="31231">Choose the shapes of the icons in the Thumbnails views.</string>
	
	<!-- Messages -->
	<string id="31300">No information available.</string>

	<!-- Window and Dialog Labels -->
	<string id="31400">Name for media source:</string>
	<string id="31402">Settings level</string>
	<string id="31404">Select group</string>
	<string id="31405">Active</string>
	<string id="31406">Channel logo</string>
	<string id="31407">Activate EPG</string>
	<string id="31408">EPG source</string>
	<string id="31409">Movies by director</string>
	<string id="31410">Show deleted</string>
	<string id="31411">Show hidden</string>
	<string id="31414">Add group</string>
	<string id="31415">Creator</string>
	<string id="31416">Karaoke Song Selector</string>
	<string id="31478">Last update</string>
	<string id="31479">Location</string>
	<string id="31480">Temperatures</string>
	<string id="31481">Weather Provider</string>
	
    <!-- Custom Options Labels -->
	<string id="31700">All Items</string>
	<string id="31701">Kodi Items</string>
	<string id="31702">Screen Widgets Items</string>
	<string id="31703">Library Data Provider Items</string>
	<string id="31711">(provided by Kodi)</string>
	<string id="31712">(provided by Screen Widgets)</string>
	<string id="31713">(provided by Library Data Provider)</string>
    
	<string id="31720">Nothing</string>
	<string id="31721">Latest Movies</string>
	<string id="31722">Latest Episodes</string>
	<string id="31723">Latest Music Videos</string>
	<string id="31724">Latest Songs</string>
	<string id="31725">Latest Albums</string>
	<string id="31726">Random Movies</string>
	<string id="31727">Random Episodes</string>
	<string id="31728">Random Music Videos</string>
	<string id="31729">Random Albums</string>
	<string id="31730">Random Artists</string>
	<string id="31731">Random Songs</string>
	<string id="31732">Random Add-ons</string>
	<string id="31733">Recommended Movies</string>
	<string id="31734">Recommended Episodes</string>
	<string id="31735">Recommended Music Videos</string>
	<string id="31736">Recommended Albums</string>
	<string id="31737">Recent Movies</string>
	<string id="31738">Recent Episodes</string>
	<string id="31739">Recent Music Videos</string>
	<string id="31740">Recent Albums</string>

	<string id="31750">Set the name of the custom option that will appear in the menu.</string>
	<string id="31751">Set the subtitle that will appear over the custom option in the menu.</string>
	<string id="31752">Set the background image for the custom option in the menu.</string>
	<string id="31753">Set the type of custom option that you want to create, the action associated with this custom option:[CR]- Custom submenu opens another menu, which you can fill with custom options. You can use the 'Edit Submenu' button to manage this submenu.[CR]- Custom items opens a window with items (such as movies, music albums) form a selected source, so you can fill a view with random albums or recommended episodes. You can use the 'Choose Items' button to select different sources for these items.[CR]- Custom action allows you to execute built-in functions from Kodi. You can use the 'Create Command' button to create these actions.</string>
	<string id="31754">Set the name of the window that is opened by this custom option.</string>
	<string id="31755">Set the source pattern that defines the properties that provide the items. The number in this pattern should be represented by '%d', so Revolve can extract the item-information from the properties and display them in a window.</string>
	<string id="31756">Set the plug-in that provides the items. You should write down the complete call to the plug-in, including arguments, but you should exclude the 'plug-in://' part of the call.</string>
	<string id="31757">Set the unique identifier of the submenu. The whole submenu is linked to this identifier. You can link an option to an existing submenu by copying the submenu's identifier, or you can loose a submenu by removing this identifier. An identifier should consist only of alphanumeric characters (so no spaces, no punctuation marks, no strange characters).</string>
	<string id="31758">Set the Kodi built-in function that should be executed when this custom option is selected. You can edit this command or use the 'Create Command' button to create a new custom command.</string>
	<string id="31759">Confirm the settings of this custom option and return to the Skin Settings menu.</string>
	<string id="31760">Discard the changes made in the settings of this custom option and return to the Skin Settings menu.</string>
	<string id="31761">Open the Custom Action Editor to create a new action for this custom option.</string>
	<string id="31762">Open the Custom Items Editor to select a source to provide items for this custom option.</string>
	<string id="31763">Open the Custom Submenu Editor to create or edit the submenu that is accessible through this custom command.</string>
	<string id="31764">Clear all the settings for this custom command.</string>
	<string id="31765">Enable or disable this help text.</string>
	<string id="31766">Close the Custom Submenu Editor and return to the Custom Option Editor.</string>
    <string id="31767">Enable this option in this submenu. You should provide a name and an action to make this custom option do something useful.</string>
    <string id="31768">Edit this custom submenu option. You can set the name and subtitle of this option, and you can enter the action that is executed when this option is chosen in the submenu.</string>
    <string id="31769">Use the scrollbar to quickly move through the list of options.</string>
	<string id="31770">Set the type of custom option that you want to create, the action associated with this custom option:[CR]- Custom items opens a window with items (such as movies, music albums) form a selected source, so you can fill a view with random albums or recommended episodes. You can use the 'Choose Items' button to select different sources for these items.[CR]- Custom action allows you to execute built-in functions from Kodi. You can use the 'Create Command' button to create these actions.</string>
	<string id="31771">Confirm the settings in this window and return to the Custom Option Editor.</string>
	<string id="31772">Discard the changes made in this window and return to the Custom Option Editor.</string>
	<string id="31773">Select the custom action that you want to connect to your custom option, or select the 'Custom Command' option in the list so you can enter a command.</string>
	<string id="31774">Select the items for this custom action. The selected items will be displayed in a window when the associated custom action is selected.</string>
	<string id="31775">Filter the list of items by the provider (the script or plug-in that provides the items) of the items.</string>
	<string id="31776">Select the playlist that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31777">Select the image that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31778">Select the file that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31779">Select the path that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31780">Select the addon that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31781">Enter the string that is used in the highlighted action.</string>
	<string id="31782">Filter the list of actions by the kind of action that you want to create.</string>
	<string id="31783">Enter a custom built-in command for this custom action.</string>
	<string id="31784">Exit Menu accessible</string>
	<string id="31785">Enable the exit menu in the circle of the Home Menu. This exit menu gives you fast access to all the exit options. If this menu is enabled, you can access it by pressing 'left' on the Exit-option in the Home Menu.</string>
	<string id="31786">Next Aired information available</string>
	<string id="31787">Enable the 'Next Aired' information in the circle of the Home Menu. If this option is enabled, you can access it by pressing 'left' on the Live TV-option in the Home Menu.</string>
	<string id="31788">Busy animation</string>
	<string id="31789">Show debug list border</string>
	<string id="31790">Open the TV guide</string>
	<string id="31791">Open the radio guide</string>
	<string id="31792">Open the TV recordings</string>
	<string id="31793">Open the radio recordings</string>
	<string id="31794">Open the TV timers</string>
	<string id="31795">Open the radio timers</string>
	<string id="31796">Open the TV search window</string>
	<string id="31797">Open the radio search window</string>
	<string id="31798">Dialog animation</string>
	<string id="31799">Shape of icons in thumbnails view</string>
    
	<string id="31800">Custom Option Editor</string>
	<string id="31801">Custom Action Editor</string>
	<string id="31802">Background Image</string>
	<string id="31803">Custom Submenu</string>
	<string id="31804">Custom Items</string>
	<string id="31805">Custom Command</string>
	<string id="31806">Edit Submenu</string>
	<string id="31807">Choose Items</string>
	<string id="31808">Create Command</string>
	<string id="31809">Custom Submenu Editor</string>
	<string id="31810">Custom Items Editor</string>
	<string id="31811">TV/Radio Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31812">Video Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31813">Music Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31814">Picture Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31815">Program Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31816">Menu Option Related Actions</string>
	<string id="31817">Miscellaneous Actions</string>
	<string id="31818">Kodi Control Actions</string>
	<string id="31819">Custom Command</string>
	<string id="31820">Open live tv</string>
	<string id="31821">Open the EPG timeline</string>
	<string id="31822">Open the TV channels</string>
	<string id="31823">Open the radio channels</string>
	<string id="31824">Open the recordings</string>
	<string id="31825">Open the timers</string>
	<string id="31826">Open the searches</string>
	<string id="31827">Open your videos</string>
	<string id="31828">Open the video library</string>
	<string id="31829">Open the movies library</string>
	<string id="31830">Open the TV shows library</string>
	<string id="31831">Open the music videos library</string>
	<string id="31832">Open the video playlists</string>
	<string id="31833">Open the video add-ons</string>
	<string id="31834">Open the video files</string>
	<string id="31835">Open your video playlist</string>
	<string id="31836">Play a dvd</string>
	<string id="31837">Update the complete video library</string>
	<string id="31838">Update the video library with the selected path</string>
	<string id="31839">Clean the video library</string>
	<string id="31840">Open your music</string>
	<string id="31841">Open the music library</string>
	<string id="31842">Open the music playlists</string>
	<string id="31843">Open the music add-ons</string>
	<string id="31844">Open the music files</string>
	<string id="31845">Open your music playlist</string>
	<string id="31846">Rip a cd</string>
	<string id="31847">Update the music library</string>
	<string id="31848">Clean the music library</string>
	<string id="31849">Open your pictures</string>
	<string id="31850">Start a normal slideshow</string>
	<string id="31851">Start a random slideshow</string>
	<string id="31852">Start a normal, recursive slideshow</string>
	<string id="31853">Start a random recursive slideshow</string>
	<string id="31854">Open your programs</string>
	<string id="31855">Open executable add-ons</string>
	<string id="31856">Run external program</string>
	<string id="31857">Run external program and wait</string>
	<string id="31858">Open Favourites</string>
	<string id="31859">Open Weather</string>
	<string id="31860">Open Addon Browser</string>
	<string id="31861">Open File Manager</string>
	<string id="31862">Open Settings</string>
	<string id="31863">Activate the screen saver</string>
	<string id="31864">Take a screenshot</string>
	<string id="31865">Mute</string>
	<string id="31866">Eject the tray in your device</string>
	<string id="31867">Wake device on local network</string>
	<string id="31868">Execute a shell command</string>
	<string id="31869">Execute a shell command and wait</string>
	<string id="31870">Refresh RSS Feeds</string>
	<string id="31871">Reload the current skin</string>
	<string id="31872">Minimize Kodi</string>
	<string id="31873">Log off user</string>
	<string id="31874">Suspend your device</string>
	<string id="31875">Hibernate your device</string>
	<string id="31876">Restart Kodi</string>
	<string id="31877">Quit Kodi</string>
	<string id="31878">Reboot your device</string>
	<string id="31879">Shut down your device</string>
	<string id="31880">Enter a custom command</string>
	<string id="31881">Choose Playlist</string>
	<string id="31882">Choose Image</string>
	<string id="31883">Choose File</string>
	<string id="31884">Choose Path</string>
	<string id="31885">Choose Addon</string>
	<string id="31886">Enter Value</string>
	<string id="31887">Custom Items Editor</string>
	<string id="31888">Circle Items Editor</string>
	<string id="31889">From skin properties</string>
	<string id="31890">From a plug-in</string>
	<string id="31891">Window title</string>
	<string id="31892">Source description</string>
	<string id="31893">Plug-in</string>
	<string id="31894">Custom Submenu Editor</string>
	<string id="31895">Menu title</string>
	<string id="31896">Menu identifier</string>
	<string id="31897">Reset all the settings on this page to their default values.</string>
	<string id="31898">Settings Reset Confirmation</string>
	<string id="31899">Are you sure that you want to reset these settings to their default values?</string>
	
	<!-- Signs / Icons / Short Label Text -->
	<string id="31900">Items</string>
	<string id="31901">Min</string>
	<string id="31902">Shows</string>
	<string id="31903">Page</string>
	<string id="31904">?</string>
	<string id="31905">!</string>
	<string id="31906">Action</string>
	<string id="31907">Side Menu</string>
	<string id="31908">Create</string>
	<string id="31909">Top Menu</string>
	<string id="31910">Command</string>
	<string id="31911">kb/s</string>
	<string id="31912">Now</string>
	<string id="31913">Category</string>
	<string id="31914">Parameter</string>
	<string id="31915">Close</string>
	<string id="31916">f/</string>
	<string id="31917">&lt;</string>
	<string id="31918">&gt;</string>
	<string id="31919">Back</string>
	<string id="31920">Stop</string>
	<string id="31921">Rewind</string>
	<string id="31922">Pause</string>
	<string id="31923">Fast Forward</string>
	<string id="31924">DVD Menu</string>
	<string id="31925">Visualisation Presets</string>
	<string id="31926">Visualisation Settings</string>
	<string id="31927">information is available</string>
	<string id="31928">Names in view</string>
	<string id="31929">Wild</string>
	<string id="31930">License</string>
	
	<string id="31931">Drop list</string>
	<string id="31932">Circle list</string>
	<string id="31933">Landscape list</string>
	<string id="31934">Revolve list</string>
	<string id="31935">Thumbnails list</string>
	<string id="31936">Panels list</string>
	<string id="31937">Gallery list</string>
	<string id="31938">Rotate list</string>
	<string id="31939">Banners list</string>
    
	<string id="31948">A</string>
	<string id="31949">P</string>
	<string id="31950">M</string>
	<string id="31951">Arrows</string>
	<string id="31952">Circles</string>
	<string id="31953">Spiral</string>
	<string id="31954">Squares</string>
</strings>
