<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.revolve" version="5.0.1" name="Revolve" provider-name="ransomed, mKo, relyter, Malthus">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
        <import addon="script.revolve.service" version="1.1.2" />
        <import addon="script.cu.lrclyrics" version="2.0.12" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.favourites" version="7.1.1" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.globalsearch" version="5.0.0" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.grab.fanart" version="0.14.1" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.rss.editor" version="2.0.4" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="6.0.12" optional="true" />
        <import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.0.6" optional="true" />
        <import addon="service.scrobbler.lastfm" version="0.0.4" optional="true" />
        <import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.29" optional="true" />
	</requires>

	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
	</extension>
	
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Revolve je grafický vzhled založený na otáčení.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Revolve es una skin centrada en la revolución.</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Revolve on ulkoasu, jonka innoituksena toimii pyörimisliike.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Revolve est un habillage centré sur la rotation.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Revolve est un habillage centré autour de la révolution.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt_LT">Revolve yra teminė išvaizda orientuota į revoliuciją.</summary>
        <summary lang="ms_MY">Revolve merupakan kulit yang berasaskan revolution.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Revolve is een skin gecenterd rondom revolutie.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Revolve jest skórą skupioną wokół obracania.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution (menus, lists and views rotate and spin).[CR][CR]Revolve is not designed for mouse- or touch-control.[CR][CR]Concept and graphics by ransomed, additional graphics by Malthus / Skin by ransomed, mKo, relyter, and Malthus. Foundation (skin) by Hitcher, and textures courtesy of Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution (menus, lists and views rotate and spin).[CR][CR]Revolve is not designed for mouse- or touch-control.[CR][CR]Concept and graphics by ransomed, additional graphics by Malthus / Skin by ransomed, mKo, relyter, and Malthus. Foundation (skin) by Hitcher, and textures courtesy of Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Revolve is a skin centered around revolution (menus, lists and views rotate and spin).[CR][CR]Revolve is not designed for mouse- or touch-control.[CR][CR]Concept and graphics by ransomed, additional graphics by Malthus / Skin by ransomed, mKo, relyter, and Malthus. Foundation (skin) by Hitcher, and textures courtesy of Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Revolve es una skin centrada en la revolución (los menús, listas y vistas rotan y se revolucionan).[CR][CR]Revolve no esta diseñada para ratón ni control táctil.[CR][CR]Concepto y gráficos de ransomed, gráficos adicionales de Malthus / Skin de ransomed, mKo, relyter y Malthus. Fundación (skin) de Hitcher, y texturas cortesia de Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Revolve on ulkoasu, joka keskittyy pyöriviin valikoihin.[CR][CR]Revolvea ei ole suunniteltu hiiri- tai kosketuskäyttöön.[CR][CR]Ulkoasun konsepti ja grafiikat tulivat ransomedilta, muut grafiikat Malthusilta. Muut tekijät: ransomed, mKo, relyter ja Malthus. Ulkoasun pohjana on käytetty Hitcherin Foundation-ulkoasua ja Jezz_X:n tekstuureja.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Revolve est un habillage centré sur la révolution (menus, listes et vues tournent et vrillent).[CR][CR]Revolve n'est pas conçu pour la souris ou le tactile.[CR][CR]Concept et graphismes par ransomed, graphismes additionnels par Malthus / Habillage par ransomed, mKo, relyter, et Malthus. Foundation (l'habillage) par Hitcher, et textures aimablement de Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="lt_LT">Revolve yra teminė išvaizda orientuota į revoliuciją (meniu, sąrašai bei rodiniai vartosi ir sukasi).[CR][CR]Revolve netinka valdymui pele ar liečiamaisiais įrenginiais.[CR][CR]Koncepcija ir grafiką sukūrė ransomed, papildomą grafiką - Malthus / Teminę išvaizdą sukūrė ransomed, mKo, relyter ir Malthus. Pagrindą (teminę išvaizdą) sukūrė Hitcher, o tekstūras - Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="ms_MY">Revolve merupakan kulit yang berpusatkan putaran atau revolution (menu, senaria dan pandangan berputar-putar).[CR][CR]Revolve tidak direka untuk digunakan dengan kawalan tetikus atau sentuh.[CR][CR]Konsep dan grafik oleh ransomed, grafik tambahan oleh Malthus / Kulit oleh ransomed, mKo, relyter, dan Malthus. Tapak (kulit) oleh Hitcher, dan tekstur ihsan daripada Jezz_X.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Revolve is een skin geconcentreerd rondom revolutie (menu's, lijsten en weergaven roteren en draaien).[CR][CR] Revolve is niet ontworpen voor muis- of aanraakbesturing.[CR] [CR] Concepten en grafische afbeeldingen door Ransomed, overige graphics Door Malthus / Skin door ransomed, mKo, relyter, en Malthus. Stichting (skin) van Hitcher, en texturen met dank aan Jezz_X.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License</license>
        <source>https://github.com/Malthus/skin.revolve/</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot1.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot2.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot3.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot4.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot5.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot6.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot7.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot8.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot9.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
