<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon 
	id="skin.transparency"
	version="3.11.1"
	name="Transparency!"
	provider-name="ronie">
	<requires>
		<import	addon="xbmc.gui" version="2.11"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="1.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.logo-downloader" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.randomitems" version="1.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.recentlyadded" version="1.0.8"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin"
	defaultresolution="720p"
	defaultresolutionwide="720p"
	defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
	effectslowdown="1"
	debugging="false"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Transparency! a fanart skin for XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="cr">Transparency! fanart skin za XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Transparency! et fanart skin til XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Transparency! ein fanart skin für XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Transparency! una skin fanart per XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Transparency! skóra z naciskiem na fanart</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">Transparency! 一个充分展示同人画的XBMC皮肤</summary>
		<description lang="en">What is Transparency!? Short answer: a fanart skin. The main goal of Transparency! is showing your fanart, fullscreen, in all of the views, all of the time. Besides this, it also tries to support every neat new feature xbmc has to offer. To save everyone a lot of time and trouble hacking the xml code themselves, all of these new features are already included in the skin, pre-configured and enabled by default (wherever possible).</description>
		<description lang="cr">Što je Transparency!? Ukratko: fanart skin. Glavni cilj Transparency! skina je prikaz fanart-a, fullscreen, konstantno u svim načinima pregleda. Također, osim toga, pokušava pružiti podršku svakoj novoj mogućnosti koju XBMC podržava. Da bi svima sačuvali vrijeme i spasili ih od problema kod intervencija unutar xml koda, sve nove mogućnosti su unaprijed implementirane u skin, podešene i aktivirane po default-u (gdje god je to bilo moguće).</description>
		<description lang="da">Hvad er Transparency!? Kort svar: et fanart skin. Hovedformålet med Transparency! er at vise dit fanart, fullscreen, i alle visningsmulighederne, hele tiden. Ud over dette, vil det også forsøge at understøtte alle smarte nye features XBMC har at tilbyde. For at alle kan spare en masse tid og og besvær ved at hacke XML-koden selv, vil alle disse nye funktioner allerede være inkluderet i dette skin, præ-konfigureret og aktiveret som standard (hvis muligt). </description>
		<description lang="de">Was ist Transparency!? Einfach ausgedrückt : ein fanart skin. Das Hauptaugenmerk von Transparency! liegt darin, eure Fanarts in voller Auflösung, in allen Ansichtsvarianten, zu jeder Zeit anzuzeigen. Davon abgesehen versucht Transparency! alle neuen Features von XBMC zu unterstützen. Um dem Nutzer eine Menge arbeit mit dem editieren des xml-codes zu ersparen, sind alle (neuen) Features bereits in den skin integriert, vorkonfiguriert und standardmäßig aktiviert ( soweit möglich ). </description>
		<description lang="it">Cos'è Transparency!? Risposta breve: una skin ottimizzata per fanart. L'obiettivo principale di Transparency! è mostrare le vostre fanart, a pieno schermo, in tutte le viste, in ogni momento. Oltre a questo, cerca di supportare tutte le funzionalità più recenti che XBMC può offrire. Per consentire a tutti di risparmiare tempo e fatica, evitando gli interventi sul codice xml, queste nuove funzionalità sono già incluse nella skin, preconfigurate e attivate di default (ogni qualvolta questo sia possibile).</description>
		<description lang="pl">Czym jest Transparency!? Krótka odpowiedź: skórą dla fanartu. Głównym celem Transparency! jest pokazywanie twoich fanartów, na pełnym ekranie, w każdym widoku, przez cały czas. Skóra próbuje również wspierać wszystkie najnowsze funkcje, które XBMC ma do zaoferowania.</description>
		<description lang="zh">Transparency!是什么？简单的说：一个同人画皮肤。Transparency!的主要目标是全屏的、在所有视图、任何时间充分地展示同人画。此外，它还力求完美实现xbmc所提供的新功能。你无需自己费力去修改xml代码，所有新功能已经被皮肤支持，并默认开启（在条件允许的情况下）。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
