<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.transparency" version="4.0.5" name="Transparency!" provider-name="ronie">
	<requires>
		<import	addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.1"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="1.0.1"/>
		<import addon="script.globalsearch" version="0.1.7"/>
		<import addon="script.randomitems" version="3.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.watchlist" version="0.1.7"/>
		<import addon="service.qlock" version="0.5.3"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" debugging="false">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p"/>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Transparency! a fanart skin for XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="cr">Transparency! fanart skin za XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Transparency! et fanart skin til XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Transparency! ein fanart skin für XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Transparency! Un skin fanart para XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Transparency! Un skin de fanarts pour XBCM</summary>
		<summary lang="he">Transparency! סקין פאנארט (fanart) ל-XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Transparency! una skin fanart per XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="ja">XBMC用ファンアートスキン Transparency!</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">Transparency! XBMC 팬아트 스킨</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Transparency! een fanart skin voor XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="no">Transparency! ett fan-art skin for XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Transparency! skóra z naciskiem na fanart</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Transparency! Uma skin fanart para XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Transparency! Фан-артовый скин для XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Transparency! ett fanart skin till XBMC</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">Transparency! 一个充分展示同人画的XBMC皮肤</summary>
		<description lang="en">What is Transparency!? Short answer: a fanart skin. The main goal of Transparency! is showing your fanart, fullscreen, in all of the views, all of the time. Besides this, it also tries to support every neat new feature xbmc has to offer. To save everyone a lot of time and trouble hacking the xml code themselves, all of these new features are already included in the skin, pre-configured and enabled by default (wherever possible).</description>
		<description lang="cr">Što je Transparency!? Ukratko: fanart skin. Glavni cilj Transparency! skina je prikaz fanart-a, fullscreen, konstantno u svim načinima pregleda. Također, osim toga, pokušava pružiti podršku svakoj novoj mogućnosti koju XBMC podržava. Da bi svima sačuvali vrijeme i spasili ih od problema kod intervencija unutar xml koda, sve nove mogućnosti su unaprijed implementirane u skin, podešene i aktivirane po default-u (gdje god je to bilo moguće).</description>
		<description lang="da">Hvad er Transparency!? Kort svar: et fanart skin. Hovedformålet med Transparency! er at vise dit fanart, fullscreen, i alle visningsmulighederne, hele tiden. Ud over dette, vil det også forsøge at understøtte alle smarte nye features XBMC har at tilbyde. For at alle kan spare en masse tid og og besvær ved at hacke XML-koden selv, vil alle disse nye funktioner allerede være inkluderet i dette skin, præ-konfigureret og aktiveret som standard (hvis muligt).</description>
		<description lang="de">Was ist Transparency!? Einfach ausgedrückt : ein fanart skin. Das Hauptaugenmerk von Transparency! liegt darin, eure Fanarts in voller Auflösung, in allen Ansichtsvarianten, zu jeder Zeit anzuzeigen. Davon abgesehen versucht Transparency! alle neuen Features von XBMC zu unterstützen. Um dem Nutzer eine Menge arbeit mit dem editieren des xml-codes zu ersparen, sind alle (neuen) Features bereits in den skin integriert, vorkonfiguriert und standardmäßig aktiviert ( soweit möglich ).</description>
		<description lang="es">¿Qué es Transparency!? Respuesta corta: un skin fanart. El principal objetivo de Transparency! es mostrar tus fanarts a pantalla completa, en todas las vistas, durate todo el tiempo. Además, también trata de incluir todas las nuevas funcionalidades que ofrece xbmc. Para ahorrar a todos un montón de tiempo y los problemas implícitos que suponen la modificación del código XML, todas estas nuevas funcionalidades ya están incluidas en el skin, pre-configuradas y habilitadas por defecto (siempre que sea posible).</description>
		<description lang="fr">Qu'est-ce que Transparency!? Réponse courte : un skin de fanart. L'objectif principal de Transparency! est d'afficher vos fanarts, en plein écran, dans toute les vues, tout le temps. Derrière cela, c'est aussi essayer d'inclure toutes les nouvelles et ingénieuses fonctionnalités qu'XBMC a à offrir. Pour vous faire gagner du temps et vous épargner la peine de devoir modifier le code xml par vous même, toutes ces nouvelles fonctionnalités sont déjà intégrées dans le skin, pré-configurées et activées par défaut (lorsque cela est possible).</description>
		<description lang="he">מה זה Transparency?! התשובה הקצרה: סקין פאנארט. המטרה הראשית של Transparency! היא להראות את הפאנארט שלכם, במסך מלא, בכל אפשרויות התצוגה, כל הזמן. חוץ מזה, הסקין מנסה לתמוך בכל אפשרות חדשה שיש ל-XBMC להציע.כדי לחסוך לכולם המון זמן וצרות בפריצת קוד ה-XML בעצמם, כל האפשרויות החדשות האלה כלולות כבר בסקין, מוגדרות מראש ומופעלות כבררת מחדל (איפה שאפשר).</description>
		<description lang="it">Cos'è Transparency!? Risposta breve: una skin ottimizzata per fanart. L'obiettivo principale di Transparency! è mostrare le vostre fanart, a pieno schermo, in tutte le viste, in ogni momento. Oltre a questo, cerca di supportare tutte le funzionalità più recenti che XBMC può offrire. Per consentire a tutti di risparmiare tempo e fatica, evitando gli interventi sul codice xml, queste nuove funzionalità sono già incluse nella skin, preconfigurate e attivate di default (ogni qualvolta questo sia possibile).</description>
		<description lang="ja">Transparency!とは？簡単な回答: それはファンアートスキン。Transparency!が目指すのは、フルスクリーンやその他すべての表示 、そしてどんな時にでもあなたのファンアートを表示することです。それに加えて、XBMCが持つあらゆる素 晴らしい新機能をサポートします。各ユーザーが自らxmlコードをハックする手間を省くため、それらの新機 能は(可能な限り)スキンに含まれており、デフォルトで設定済みであり、有効となっています。</description>
		<description lang="ko">Transparency!는 무엇인가? 간단히 말하면, 팬아트 스킨이다. Transparency!의 주 목적은 당신의 팬아트, 전체화면을 모든 보기모드에서 언제나 보여주는 것이다. 또한, XBMC가 제공하는 멋진 새로운 기능들을 모두 지원하기위해 노력한다. xml 코드를 바꾸기 위해 겪는 고통과 필요한 시간을 절약시키기 위해, 모든 새로운 기능들이 스킨에 이미 내장되어 있으며, 기본적으로 미리 설정되어 사용가능하도록 되어있다.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Wat is Transparency!? Simpelweg: een fanart skin. Het voornaamste doel van Transparency! is om je fanart zo goed mogelijk weer te geven, full-screen, in alle weergaven, op alle momenten. Daarnaast streeft Transparency! er naar alle nieuwe features van XBMC te ondersteunen. Gebruikers kunnen zich de tijd en moeite besparen om zelf de xml-code te bewerken: al deze nieuwe features zijn in de skin geïntegreerd, voorgeconfigureerd en standaard geactiveerd (indien mogelijk).</description>
		<description lang="no">Hva er Transparency!? Kort svar: et fan-art skin. Hovedmålet med Transparency! er å vise din fan-art som bakgrunns bilde over alt hele tiden. Foruten dette, prøver den også å støtte alle nye fantastiske funksjoner som xbmc har å tilby. For å spare deg for en hel masse tid og problemer med omskrivning av xml-koden, så er alle disse nye funksjonene allerede inkludert i Transparency!, ferdig konfigurert og aktivert som standard (der det er mulig).</description>
		<description lang="pl">Czym jest Transparency!? Krótka odpowiedź: skórą dla fanartu. Głównym celem Transparency! jest pokazywanie twoich fanartów, na pełnym ekranie, w każdym widoku, przez cały czas. Skóra próbuje również wspierać wszystkie najnowsze funkcje, które XBMC ma do zaoferowania.</description>
		<description lang="pt">O que é Transparency!? Resposta rápida: uma skin fanart. O principal objetivo de Transparency! é exibir seu fanart, em tela cheia, em todos as visualizações, o tempo todo. Além disto, ela tenta suportar cada novo recurso que o xbmc tem a oferecer. Para economizar tempo e problemas hackeando os xmls por conta própria, todos estes recursos já estão incluídos na skin, pré-configurados e habilitados por default (onde possível).</description>
		<description lang="ru">Что такое Transparency!? Короткий ответ: фан-артовый скин. Главная задача Transparency! показывать ваши фан-арты, на полном экране, во всех ракурсах, всё время. Кроме того, мы также пытаемся поддерживать все новые возможности, предоставляемые XBMC. Для сохранения вашего времени и нервов, которые бы вы потратили, разбираясь в .xml коде, все новые функции уже добавлены в скин, настроены и включены по-умолчанию (ну или почти все).</description>
		<description lang="sv">Vad är Transparency!? Det korta svaret är: Ett fanart-vänligt skin. Det övergripande målet med Transparency! är att visa fanart i fullskärm i alla kategorier, hela tiden. Förutom det så försöker Transparency! att utnyttja varenda häftig liten funktion som finns i XBMC. För att slippa krångel med att ändra i xml-koden själv, så är de nya funktionerna inkluderade från början, förkonfigurerade och aktiverade (när det är möjligt).</description>
		<description lang="zh">Transparency!是什么？简单的说：一个同人画皮肤。Transparency!的主要目标是全屏的、在所有视图、任何时间充分地展示同人画。此外，它还力求完美实现xbmc所提供的新功能。你无需自己费力去修改xml代码，所有新功能已经被皮肤支持，并默认开启（在条件允许的情况下）。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
