<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.pm3-hd"
  version="1.3.1"
  name="PM3.HD"
  provider-name="Jezz_X, Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="2.11"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultresolution="720p"
    defaultresolutionwide="720p"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    effectslowdown="1.0"
    debugging="false"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Project Mayhem III High Definition skin by Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">PM3.HD skin (szerző: Jezz_X)</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">PM3.HD skin door Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema 'Project Mayhem III High Definition', desenvolvido por Jezz_X</summary>
    <description lang="en">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) was based on the design of the old default skin Project Mayhem III by Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]This skin was created as XBMC moved off the xbox platform onto PC's.   People were wanting to use XBMC on High Definition TV in 720p and 1080p and it came to my attention that the old default Project Mayhem III skin looked great on the low resolution xbox but looked very blocky when scaled up to Hi definition.    So PM3.HD was created to fill the gap for High definition users with our first official "stable" release of XBMC for Linux, OSX and Windows.</description>
    <description lang="hu">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) egy régi alapskinre épül (Project Mayhem III, szerző: Chokemaniac).[CR][CR]Ez a skin akkor keletkezett amikor az XBMC átváltott a PC platforma, amikor a felhasználók a nagyfelbontású (720p, 1080p) TV készülékeiken akarták élvezni az XBMC-t. Ez volt az alapskin az első "hivatalos" stabil verzióban a Linux, Windows és OSX platformokon.</description>
    <description lang="nl">PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) is gebaseerd op het design van de oude standaard skin (PM3) door Chokemaniac.[CR]  Deze skin werd ontworpen toen XBMC van het xbox platform naar PC's verhuisde. Mensen wilden toen XBMC gebruiken op HD TVs in 720p en 1080p en de originele PM3 skin werd slecht weergegeven in deze hoge resoluties. Dit lag aan de de basis van de PM3.HD skin</description>
    <description lang="pt">O tema PM3.HD (Project Mayhem III High Definition) foi baseado no desenho do velho tema padrão do XBMC, 'Project Mayhem III', desenvolvido por Chokemaniac.[CR][CR]Este tema foi criado quando o XBMC deixou de ser desenvolvido para a plataforma xbox.   A comunidade queria usar o XBMC em TVs de alta-definição (720p and 1080p) e chamou à atenção para o facto que o velho tema 'Project Mayhem III' era visualmente agradável na xbox, mas ficava horrível quando usado em aparelhos capazes de alta-definição.    Assim, o tema PM3.HD foi criado para preencher o vazio existente que os utilizadores notaram na primeira versão estável para Linux, OSX e Windows, plataformas já com capacidade para alta-definição.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
