<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
	id="skin.titan"
	version="3.2.66"
	name="Titan MediaBrowser"
	provider-name="marcelveldt">
	<requires>
		<import version="5.3.0" addon="xbmc.gui"/>		
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.29" />
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.6.9" />
		<import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.0.4"/> 
		<import addon="script.grab.fanart" version="0.13.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.4"/>
		<import addon="script.titanskin.helpers" version="1.6.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false">		
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de">MediaPortal's Titan Skin portiert für Kodi mit jeder Menge Funktionen und einer vollständigen MediaBrowser Integration.</summary>
		<summary lang="en">MediaPortal's Titan skin ported to Kodi enriched with lot's of features and full integration of MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">MediaPortal's Titan skin ported to Kodi enriched with lot's of features and full integration of MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">MediaPortal's Titan skin ported to Kodi enriched with lot's of features and full integration of MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Titan de MediaPortal porté vers Kodi et enrichi de nombreuses fonctions et de l'intégration complète du navigateur multimédia.</summary>
		<summary lang="he">המעטפת Titan שבמקור נוצרה עבור MediaPortal, שודרגה ביכולות רבות ושילוב מלא של MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<summary lang="it">La skin di MediaPortal Titan arriva su Kodi arricchita con molte feature e piena integrazione di MediaBrowser</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">MediaPortal'o Titan teminė išvaizda perkelta į Kodi ir papildyta daugybe funkcijų bei pilna MediaBrowser integracija.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">De Titanskin van MediaPortal is geconverteerd naar Kodi en verrijkt met talloze functionaliteiten</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Skóra Titan przeniesiona z programu MediaPortal do Kodi, wzbogacona o dodatkowe funkcje i pełną integrację z MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">O porte da skin Titan para o Kodi enriquecida com varias funcionalidades e total integração do MediaBrowser.</summary>
		<description lang="de">Machen Sie das meiste aus ihrer Kodi-Installation mit dem Titan Skin. Ursprünglich eine Portierung des Standard MediaPortal Skins , nun mit jeder Menge eigenen Funktionen und Anpassungen.</description>
		<description lang="en">Get the most out of your Kodi installation with the Titan skin, originally a port of the standard MediaPortal skin now has lot's of features on his own.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Get the most out of your Kodi installation with the Titan skin, originally a port of the standard MediaPortal skin now has lots of features on his own.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Tirez le maximum de votre installation Kodi avec l'habillage Titan, à l'origine un portage de l'habillage standard MediaPortal avec maintenant de nombreuses fonctions propres.</description>
		<description lang="he">ניצול מלוא הפוטנציאל של Kodi בעזרת המעטפת Titan, במקור הינה גרסה מותאמת עבור Kodi של המעטפת הסטנדרטית של MediaPortal שעתה בעלת תכונות רבות משל עצמה.</description>
		<description lang="it">Ottieni il massimo dalla tua installazione di Kodi con la skin Titan, originariamente un port della skin predefinita di MediaPortal che ha ora molte caratteristiche uniche.</description>
		<description lang="lt">Pilnai išnaudokite Kodi galimybes su Titan temine išvaizda, kuri buvo perkelta iš standartinės MediaPortal teminės išvaizdos ir dabar turi daugybę savų funkcijų.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Haal het maximale uit je Kodi installatie met de Titan MediaBrowser skin. Begonnen als een port van Mediaportal is uitgebreid met talloze eigen functies zoals de integratie van MediaBrowser etc. </description>
		<description lang="pl">Wykorzystaj w pełni możliwości Kodi przy pomocy skóry Titan, oryginalnie bezpośrednio przeniesionej z programu MediaPortal, a teraz rozszerzonej o wiele dodatkowych funkcji.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Tenha o melhor da instalação do Kodi com a skin Titan, originalmente um porte da skin MediaPortal mas agora com varias funções proprias.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=201061</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source></source>
	</extension>
</addon>