<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.bello.9" version="9.0.5" name="Bello 9" provider-name="Nessus">
  <requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.16.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="4.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.embuary.helper" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="resource.images.languageflags.colour" version="0.0.4"/>
		<import addon="resource.images.weathericons.outline" version="0.0.6"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" effectslowdown="0.75" debugging="false">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-Share Alike 4.0 International License</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=198</forum>
    <email>nessus85100 at hotmail dot com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/Nessus85100/skin.bello.9</source>
    <news>For a full list of changes visit https://github.com/Nessus85100/skin.bello.9/commits/master</news>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
    <summary lang="af">&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;apos;n GUI vir Kodi Media Sentrum</summary>
    <summary lang="af_ZA">&apos;n GUI vir Kodi Media Sentrum</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">واجهة رسومية لمركز الوسائط Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">واجهة رسومية لمركز الوسائط Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Потребителски интерфейс за Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Потребителски интерфейс за Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Una interfície gràfica per a l&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;apos;Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Una interfície gràfica per a l&apos;Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="da">En GUI til Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">En grafisk brugerflade til Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Ein GUI für das Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Ein GUI für das Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Ένα Γραφικό Περιβάλλον για το Κέντρο Πολυμέσων Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="en">A GUI for Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">A GUI for Kodi Media Centre</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">A GUI for Kodi Media Centre</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">A GUI for Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Una interfaz gráfica para Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Una interfaz gráfica para Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Un thème pour Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Une IUG pour le centre multimédia Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Un thème pour Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Un GUI para Centro de Medios Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Un GUI para Centro de Medios Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="he">ממשק משתמש עבור Kodi מדיה סנטר</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">ממשק משתמש עבור Kodi מדיה סנטר</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Felszín az  Kodi Média centerhez</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Felszín az Kodi Média centerhez</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">GUI untuk Sentra Media Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Un Interfaccia per Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Una GUI per Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Kodi メディアセンター用 GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">Kodi メディアセンター用 GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Kodi Media Center를 위한 그래픽 사용자 인터페이스</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Kodi Media Center를 위한 그래픽 사용자 인터페이스</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Kodi media centro GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Kodi media centro GUI</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">GUI untuk Pusat Media Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">GUI untuk Pusat Media Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Een gebruikersinterface voor Kodi Media Center </summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Een gebruikersinterface voor Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Interfejs użytkownika dla Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Interfejs użytkownika dla Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Uma Interface para o Centro de Média Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Uma interface gráfica para o Kodi Media Center</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Uma Interface para o Centro de Média Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обложка для Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка для Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Uporabniški vmesnik za medijsko središče Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Uporabniški vmesnik za medijsko središče Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Ett grafiskt användargränssnitt för Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Ett grafiskt användargränssnitt för Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="th">ส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ สำหรับศูนย์รวมสื่อ Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">ส่วนติดต่อผู้ใช้ สำหรับศูนย์รวมสื่อ Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Kodi Media Center İçin Arayüz</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Kodi Media Center İçin Arayüz</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Kodi媒体中心的一个图形用户界面</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">Kodi媒体中心的一个图形用户界面</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">一個 Kodi 多媒體中心的圖形介面</summary>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτή ειναι η 9η έκδοση του Bello για το Κέντρο Πολυμέσων Kodi. Στόχος του Bello 9 είναι να μεγιστοποιήσει την ψυχαγωγική σας εμπειρία μέσω του ΝΕΟΥ γρήγορου, κομψού, μοναδικού και ενοποιημένου περιβάλλοντός του, παρέχοντας στους χρήστες ένα υψηλό επίπεδο προσαρμογής και πολλά νεα χαρακτηριστικά και λειτουργίες!.</description>
    <description lang="en">This is the 9th generation of Bello skin for Kodi. Bello 9 is aiming to maximize your Kodi entertainment experience with its NEW Unique, Clean and Elegant interface while providing users a highly customization level and lots of cool features!</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">This is the 9th generation of Bello skin for Kodi. Bello 9 is aiming to maximize your Kodi entertainment experience with its NEW Unique, Clean and Elegant interface while providing users a highly customization level and lots of cool features!</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This is the 9th generation of Bello skin for Kodi. Bello 9 is aiming to maximize your Kodi entertainment experience with its NEW Unique, Clean and Elegant interface while providing users a highly customization level and lots of cool features!</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This is the 9th generation of Bello skin for Kodi. Bello 9 is aiming to maximize your Kodi entertainment experience with its NEW Unique, Clean and Elegant interface while providing users a highly customization level and lots of cool features!</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Esta es la octava generacion de la skin Bello para Kodi. Bello 8 esta enfocada para maximizar tu experiencia de entretenmiento con Kodi con su interfaz NUEVA, Única, Limpia y Elegante mientras le da a los usuarios gran nivel de personalización ¡y un montón de características molonas!</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Il s&apos;agit de la 8ème génération de skin Bello pour Kodi. Bello 8 vise à maximiser votre expérience de divertissement Kodi avec sa NOUVELLE interface unique, propre et élégante tout en offrant aux utilisateurs un niveau de personnalisation élevé et de nombreuses fonctionnalités intéressantes !</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Ini adalah skin Bello generasi ke-8 untuk Kodi. Bello 8 bertujuan untuk memaksimalkan pengalaman hiburan Kodi Anda dengan antarmuka BARU yang Unik, Bersih, dan Elegan sambil memberikan tingkat penyesuaian yang tinggi kepada pengguna dan banyak fitur keren!</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questa è l&apos;ottava generazione della skin Bello per Kodi. Bello 8 mira a massimizzare la tua esperienza di intrattenimento Kodi con la sua NUOVA interfaccia unica, pulita ed elegante, fornendo agli utenti un livello di personalizzazione elevato e molte funzioni interessanti!</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Это восьмое поколение обложки Bello для Kodi. Bello 8 старается предоставить лучший опыт развлечений Kodi своим НОВЫМ уникальным, чистым и элегантным интерфейсом, при этом давая пользователем обширные настройки для кастомизации и кучу крутых функций!</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">这是 Kodi 的第 8 代 Bello 皮肤。Bello 8 旨在通过其全新的独特、干净和优雅的界面，最大限度地提高您的 Kodi 娱乐体验，同时为用户提供高度定制级别和许多炫酷功能！</description>
    <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Ποντίκι, Παιχνιδια και οθόνες αφης δεν υποστηρίζονται. Με την εγκατάσταση αυτού του γραφικού περιβάλλοντος συμφωνείτε ότι δεν το χρησιμοποιείτε με οποιονδήποτε τρόπο για εμπορικούς σκοπούς χωρίς την προηγούμενη συγκατάθεσή μου. Δεν έχω καμμία σχέση με κανένα προσαρμοσμένο λογισμικό Kodi (Build) και δεν θα παρέχω καμία υποστήριξη σε απαγορευμένα ή παράνομα πρόσθετα τρίτων.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Mouse, Games and touchscreen use are not supported. With the installation of this skin you agree that you don&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;apos;t use it in any way for comercial purposes without my prior consentse. I&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;apos;m not associated with any available Kodi build and i won&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;apos;t give any support to blacklisted, banned or illegal third party addons.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">Mouse, Games and touchscreen use are not supported. With the installation of this skin you agree that you don&apos;t use it in any way for comercial purposes without my prior consentse. I&apos;m not associated with any available Kodi build and i won&apos;t give any support to blacklisted, banned or illegal third party addons.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Mouse, Games and touchscreen use are not supported. With the installation of this skin you agree that you don&apos;t use it in any way for comercial purposes without my prior consentse. I&apos;m not associated with any available Kodi build and i won&apos;t give any support to blacklisted, banned or illegal third party addons.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">Mouse, Games and touchscreen use are not supported. With the installation of this skin you agree that you don&apos;t use it in any way for comercial purposes without my prior consentse. I&apos;m not associated with any available Kodi build and i won&apos;t give any support to blacklisted, banned or illegal third party addons.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">No se soporta Ratón, Juegos ni pantallas táctiles. Al instalar esta skin estás de acuerdo en no usarla de ninguna manera para fines comerciales sin mi previo consentimiento. No estoy asociado con ninguna construcción de Kodi y no daré ningun soporte a add-ons de terceros ilegales, baneados o en lista negra.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">L&apos;utilisation de la souris, commandes de jeux et de écran tactile n&apos;est pas prise en charge. Avec l&apos;installation de ce skin, vous acceptez de ne pas l&apos;utiliser à des fins commerciales sans mon consentement préalable. Je ne suis associé à aucune version de Kodi disponible et je ne fournirai aucun support aux addons tiers sur liste noire, interdits ou illégaux.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="id_ID">Penggunaan Mouse, Game, dan layar sentuh tidak didukung. Dengan pemasangan skin ini Anda setuju bahwa Anda tidak menggunakannya dengan cara apa pun untuk tujuan komersial tanpa persetujuan saya sebelumnya. Saya tidak terkait dengan build Kodi apa pun yang tersedia dan saya tidak akan memberikan dukungan apa pun kepada add-on pihak ketiga yang masuk daftar hitam, dilarang, atau ilegal.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it_IT">L&apos;utilizzo di mouse, giochi e touchscreen non è supportato. Con l&apos;installazione di questa skin accetti di non utilizzarla in alcun modo per scopi commerciali senza il mio previo consenso. Non sono associato a nessuna build disponibile di Kodi e non fornirò alcun supporto per add-on di terze parti inseriti nella lista nera, vietati o illegali.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Игры, управление мышью и сенсорным экраном не поддерживаются. Устанавливая данную обложку Вы даёте согласие, что не будете её использовать для каких-либо коммерческих целей без моего согласия. Я не связан ни с какой-либо доступной сборкой Kodi, и я никогда не добавлю какой-либо поддержки запрещённым или незаконным дополнениям от третьих лиц.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">不支持使用鼠标、游戏和触摸屏。安装此皮肤表示您同意，未经我事先同意，您不得以任何方式将其用于商业目的。我与任何可用的 Kodi 发行版都没有关联，我不会对列入黑名单、被禁止或非法的第三方插件提供任何支持。</disclaimer>
  </extension>
</addon>
