<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.back-row" version="4.0.3" name="Back Row" provider-name="Sharpe and DJDafreund">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.19"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.4.6"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.11"/>
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="5.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.tvtunes" version="3.0.2"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" debugging="false" effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
 	  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be">Back Row skin by Sharpe and DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="cs">Motiv Back Row vytvořen Sharpe a DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="da">Back Row skin af Sharpe og DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Back Row skin von Sharpe und DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Κέλυφος Back Row από τους Sharpe και DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Back Row skin by Sharpe and DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Back Row skin por Sharpe y DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">Back Row 스킨 제작 Sharpe and DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Skóra Back Row autorstwa Sharpe i DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="sk">Vzhľad Back Row, vytvorili ho Sharpe a DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Back Row skal av Sharpe och DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">Sharpe和DJDafreund的Back Row皮肤</summary>
		<description lang="be">Back Row is all about recapturing the magic of going to the cinema in your own home. The skin has been designed with this aim in mind but has taken on board many good ideas and suggestions from the XBMC community. Over the years it has become a polished theme that can be easily customised to suit your needs. So go grab some popcorn and fool around on the Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="cs">Back Row motiv je celý o navození atmosféry kina ve vašem obýváku. Motiv byl navržen s tímhle cílem, ale také byl brán v zřetel na nápady a připomínky z XBMC komunity. Za ty roky se stal tento motiv natolik vypilován, že může být velice snadno upraven dle vašich představ. Tak popadněte popcorn a pojte se bavit s Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="da">Back Row handler om at genfange magien ved at gå i biografen i dit eget hjem. Skin'et er blevet designet med dette mål for øje, men har adopteret mange gode ideer og forslag fra XBMC-community'et. I løbet af årene er det blevet et poleret tema, som nemt kan tilpasses så det passer til dine behov. Så smid nogle popcorn i mikroovnen og hyg dig på bagsædet.</description>
		<description lang="de">Back Row geht es darum, die Magie des Kinogehens ins eigene Zuhause zu bringen. Der Skin wurde mit diesem Ziel entwickelt, es wurde aber viele gute Ideen und Vorschlägen aus der XBMC community mit an Bord genommen. Über die Jahre wurde es ein ausgefeiltes Thema, welches einfach an die eigenen Bedürfnisse angepasst werden kann. Popcorn geschnappt und es sich gemütlich gemacht auf der Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το Back Row έχει ως στόχο τη μαγεία του να πηγαίνει κανείς στον κινηματογράφο μέσα στο ίδιο του το σπίτι. Το κέλυφος έχει σχεδιαστεί κατ' αυτόν τον τρόπο, αλλά έχουν προστεθεί και πολλές ιδέες και προτάσεις από την κοινότητα του XBMC. Με τα χρόνια έχει γίνει ένα καλοσχεδιασμένο μοτίβο το οποίο μπορεί να προσαρμοστεί για να ταιριάζει στις ανάγκες του καθενός. Γι'αυτό αρπάξτε τα ποπ κορν και κάντε το κέφι σας με το Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="en">Back Row is all about recapturing the magic of going to the cinema in your own home. The skin has been designed with this aim in mind but has taken on board many good ideas and suggestions from the XBMC community. Over the years it has become a polished theme that can be easily customised to suit your needs. So go grab some popcorn and fool around on the Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="es">Back Row (Fila de atrás), trata sobre recuperar la magia de ir al cine sin salir de casa. La piel ha sido diseñada con este objetivo, pero también se ha tenido en cuenta las sugerencias y muchas buenas ideas de la comunidad de XBMC. Con los años se ha convertido en un tema muy trabajado que se puede personalizar fácilmente para adaptarse a sus necesidades. Así que vayan a por palomitas y pasen un rato en la última fila.</description>
		<description lang="it">L'obiettivo di Back Row è portare la magia del cinema a casa vostra. Questa skin è stata creata con in mente questo obiettivo ma sono state aggiunte molte buone idee e suggerimenti dalla comunità di XBMC. Negli anni è diventato un tema raffinato che può essere facilmente personalizzato per adattarsi alle vostre esigenze. Quindi prendete dei popcorn e divertitevi con Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="pl">BackRow to przeniesienie magii chodzenia do kina do własnego domu. Ten pomysł posłużył do zaprojektowania tej skóry, ale również wcielił w życie wiele dobrych pomysłów i sugestii społeczności XBMC. Przez lata stała się wypolerowanym tematem, który może być łatwo dostosowany do własnych potrzeb. Chwyć więc popcorn i zrelaksuj się w tylnym rzędzie (Back Row).</description>
		<description lang="sk">Back Row je o tom znovu nadobudnúť ten magický pocit, ako by ste šli do kina, u vás doma. Tento vzhľad bol navrhnutý s ohľadom na to, ale prijal tiež mnohé skvelé nápady a návrhy XBMC komunity. V priebehu rokov sa stal vyladeným motívom, ktorý je možné jednoducho prispôsobiť, aby spĺňal vaše potreby. Tak vezmite si pukance a pohrajte sa chvíľu s Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="zh">Back Row让你在家体验到上电影院的感觉。皮肤基于此目标并吸收了XBMC社区的不少好的意见和建议。经过多年完善，它已能很容易地定制以满足你的需求。那么，赶紧抓一把爆米花来体验Back Row吧。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="be">Should cause no issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs">Neměl by způsobit zádné problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da">Burde ikke giver problemer</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Sollte keine Probleme bereiten</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el">Λογικά δε θα υπάρξει πρόβλημα</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Should cause no issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Podría no causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he">לא אמור לגרום לבעיות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it">Non dovrebbe causare alcun problema</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl">Nie powinno powodować problemów</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk">Nemali by byť spôsobené žiadne problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv">Borde inte orsaka några problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh">应该不会有问题</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
