<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.back-row" version="4.0.1" name="Back Row" provider-name="Sharpe and DJDafreund">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.2"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.1"/>
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.2.0"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="1.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="4.1.15"/>
		<import addon="script.tvtunes" version="1.0.15"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" debugging="false" effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
 	  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be">Back Row skin by Sharpe and DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Back Row skin von Sharpe und DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Κέλυφος Back Row από τους Sharpe και DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Back Row skin by Sharpe and DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Back Row skin por Sharpe y DJDafreund</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">Sharpe和DJDafreund的Back Row皮肤</summary>
		<description lang="be">Back Row is all about recapturing the magic of going to the cinema in your own home. The skin has been designed with this aim in mind but has taken on board many good ideas and suggestions from the XBMC community. Over the years it has become a polished theme that can be easily customised to suit your needs. So go grab some popcorn and fool around on the Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="de">Back Row geht es um die Magie des Kinogehens ins eigene Zuhause zu bringen. Der Skin wurde mit diesem Ziel entwickelt, es wurde aber viele gute Ideen und Vorschlägen aus der XBMC community mit an Bord genommen. Über die Jahre wurde es ein ausgefeiltes Thema, welches einfach an die eigenen Bedürfnisse angepasst werden kann. Popkorn geschnappt und es sich gemütlich gemacht auf der Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το Back Row έχει ως στόχο τη μαγεία του να πηγαίνει κανείς στον κινηματογράφο μέσα στο ίδιο του το σπίτι. Το κέλυφος έχει σχεδιαστεί κατ' αυτόν τον τρόπο, αλλά έχουν προστεθεί και πολλές ιδέες και προτάσεις από την κοινότητα του XBMC. Με τα χρόνια έχει γίνει ένα καλοσχεδιασμένο μοτίβο το οποίο μπορεί να προσαρμοστεί για να ταιριάζει στις ανάγκες του καθενός. Γι'αυτό αρπάξτε τα ποπ κορν σας και κάντε το κέφι με το Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="en">Back Row is all about recapturing the magic of going to the cinema in your own home. The skin has been designed with this aim in mind but has taken on board many good ideas and suggestions from the XBMC community. Over the years it has become a polished theme that can be easily customised to suit your needs. So go grab some popcorn and fool around on the Back Row.</description>
		<description lang="es">Back Row (Fila de atrás), trata sobre recuperar la magia de ir al cine sin salir de casa. La piel ha sido diseñada con este objetivo, pero también se ha tenido en cuenta las sugerencias y muchas buenas ideas de la comunidad de XBMC. Con los años se ha convertido en un tema muy trabajado que se puede personalizar fácilmente para adaptarse a sus necesidades. Así que vayan a por palomitas y pasen un rato en la última fila.</description>
		<description lang="zh">Back Row让你在家体验到上电影院的感觉。皮肤基于此目标并吸收了XBMC社区的不少好的意见和建议。经过多年完善，它已能很容易地定制以满足你的需求。那么，赶紧抓一把爆米花来体验Back Row吧。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="be">Should cause no issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de">Sollte keine Probleme bereiten</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el">Λογικά δε θα υπάρξει πρόβλημα</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Should cause no issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Podría no causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh">应该不会有问题</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
